♪Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop♪
♪And then we'll shop♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪On a mission undercover
and we're in control♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪Here we go♪
Dad, this is so boring. It's just a rock
with a bunch of dead guys on it.
Come on son, one more picture.
Now smile.
(surprised cries)
What's wrong, Clover? Did you,
like, hurt yourself or something?
No, I'm fine.
Then what's with the lame rollerblading?
(gasps)
Whoa!
Watch and learn, ladies!
Oh, no. I'm so sorry. Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine. Don't worry about it.
- Wow, she's good.
- Very good.
Sure, Saturday night would be perfect,
Jason.
Cool. I'll pick you up at eight.
Did you see that?
I just got a date with Jason Roberts.
Mandy's going to so hate me. She's been
wanting to go out with him for like...
(they scream)
Whoa! Whoa!
- Oh, sorry, Jerry.
- (sighs)
No problem. That was just
the million-dollar prototype
for our new billion-dollar
surveillance satellite.
Spies, I've got
an important assignment for you.
Famous landmarks from around
the world are being stolen.
How does someone steal a landmark?
Aren't they big and kind of...
connected to the ground?
Well, our perpetrator has found
a way to shrink them,
then suck them up into the sky.
We've acquired some video
taken by tourists
who have witnessed these events.
Huh? Oops.
Now, it seems this thief
is moving from west to east,
so according to WOOHP calculations,
the Taj Mahal is the next target.
- Cool! We get to go to Mexico!
- Uh, India.
Yes.
And you will be posing as diplomats.
Here are your papers, credentials
and native costumes.
- Now, for your gadgets...
- Wow.
Today's specials include an all-in-one
lipstick and titanium Extendo-Rod...
Ugh! I look horrible in pinks.
A locator/deactivator
rhinestone headband,
turbo-fueled jet-pack backpacks,
telescopic Optic 2000 sunglasses
with built-in cam,
a laser cutter eyelash curler,
and a CADBOP.
Is that one of those
fruit-flavored snacks?
No, it's a Climb-Anything Dirt Bike
that's Octane-Powered.
Uh, one thing, Jer. How long
do you think this mission will take?
I can't be sure, actually.
As long as it takes for you to find
and stop whoever is behind this.
Well, you see,
I've got this date Saturday night,
so, it would be better for me if we
could just be back by then!
Wow, that is amazing!
It's even bigger than some of
the houses in Beverly Hills.
I don't understand why you had
to lug all your clothes with you.
Fashion crisis! I need to pick out
what to wear on my date.
Number one rule in dating:
the outfit is everything!
Wait, isn't that
the number one rule in life?
Uh-oh. It seems like Jerry
overlooked one little detail.
How are we going to get in?
We're diplomats, remember?
We have papers and credentials.
We're closed for renovations.
No one gets in!
- What do we do, now?
- I'm thinking...
Four days till Jason.
Can ya think a little faster?
Yeah! Who's up for climbing?
- How do girls move in these things?
- Don't worry. I can fix this.
You know,
since short is last year's long,
I'm thinking we market these things
and make a killing.
Alright, you guys.
Let's do what we do best.
Cool. Point me toward the gift shop!
Place looks clean.
I'm telling Jerry
that WOOHP's calculations are wrong.
Wait, what's this?
CLOVER: It's either a tracking device
or a way-cool mood ring.
- SAM: Let me see.
- (they shriek)
Look out! The walls are closing in!
So's the ceiling!
We're going to get squashed!
Quick, the door!
- ALEX: It's locked!
- SAM: Over here!
ALEX: We're not gonna make it through!
Wait! The all-in-one lipstick and
titanium Extendo-Rod should work!
I think it's time we called Jerry.
Hello, ladies.
Uh, Jer, the Taj Mahal kind of... got
away from us, if you know what we mean.
But we recovered this tracking device.
And to catch whoever is behind this,
we need you to see if its frequency
matches any other tracking devices
- elsewhere in the world.
- Let's see... Ah-ha.
Yes, yes... I'm picking up
a faint signal near the Great Wall.
- Looks like we're Peru bound.
- Uh, try China.
Hmph!
I wish it could help me find
an outfit for my date.
SAM: This locator should find
the tracking device, no problem.
Ah-ha! Here it is!
Now let's deactivate it.
Like I said, let's deactivate it...
Let me try.
There you go. And you thought I wear
these just because they look good.
- Found anything yet, Alex?
- Not yet.
Whoa. Headache!
Hey, what is that? I think I see
a black speck. Or, is it a black dot?
Nah, it's kind of like
a black piece of rice...
- Why don't you zoom in and find out?
- Oh, yeah.
ALEX: Hey, that's a black blimp!
With two people on board.
SAM: All right, spies. Time to fly!
- How are we going to get in?
- This thing's got turbo, right?
You could have warned me
you were doing that.
- Check that out!
- SAM: I have a sneaky suspicion
this is the shrinking machine
all the action is from.
And there are the people responsible.
And they're, like, two feet tall!
MAN:I don't care if you can't
locate the tracking device.
Use manual controls.
But get me my Great Wall!
Then return immediately to the island
so we can find out what's broken,
and get ready to carry out
the rest of my plan.
Yes, sir.
We've got to deactivate that machine.
SAM: This should do the trick!
- (alarm)
- What was that?!
I'll check it out.
Time for plan B!
Sally! We have invaders!
ALEX: Invader this!
- (they shriek)
- Remind me not to arm wrestle them.
Sinclair, get the one by the machine!
I'll take the other two!
- Ha! I've got you now!
- I wouldn't be so sure!
(yells)
Zap her with the Alpha X9 Ray Gun!
Oh, here comes my lunch.
(screams)
Oh, no! (screams)
It's time we stepped outside.
SAM: Got you! Now stay put.
Where am I going to go?
Quick! Zap the other two!
This is just great. How am I
going to try my clothes on for my date?
JERRY:An analysis of
the purple substance on Clover's pants
reveals this could only be the work of
one man, Diminutive Smalls.
- Diminutive who?
- Smalls.
Years ago, he was a WOOHP scientist
working on a formula
to increase strength by reducing mass.
There was a freak accident.
He and his two siblings
got shrunk by his own machine
but gained incredible strength.
It seems Diminutive has perfected the
shrinking process and wants revenge.
If only he'd gotten therapy, then the
whole world wouldn't be in this mess.
We've been picking up
an unusual level of radiation
from a small island in
the South China Sea called Jarnesia.
Our experts believe
he may have set up camp there.
That's probably the island
they were talking about.
- We'll check it out right away!
- He's dangerous, so be careful, spies.
Hey, what about me?
Yes. We're already working on
an antidote for you, Clover.
Good. In two days, I've got this
date with this guy named Jason...
I know. I know.
Did I tell you about the dimple
he's got...
Oh! So sorry! I think we're breaking up.
Goodbye!
(they laugh)
- ALEX: One... two... three...
- ALL: Hit it!
ALEX: These CADBOPs rock!
SAM: And roll!
ALL: Whoa.
Check out that creepy castle!
That's exactly what we're going to do.
This CADBOP is way cool.
Look, there's the...
welcoming committee. Uh-oh!
MAN: Ready and... fire!
Fire again!
We're in a real-life video game!
Oh, no! We're trapped!
ALEX: Not so fast!
Ha! Let's see them try to get us now!
- (they shriek)
- You and your big mouth! (screams)
Ow!
Clover, we're coming!
SAM: Follow that tank!
- Now what are we going to do?
- Maybe there's a way in from the roof.
(grunts) We can't get any traction!
(thud)
I guess these are climb
almost anything dirt bikes.
I have an idea.
This should do the trick.
That wasn't the belt I lent you, was it?
DIMINUTIVE SMALLS:
We're ready to go.
Clover, I want to thank you
for being our guinea pig.
Now that I see how well my device
works on humans...
The world's greatest monuments
all in one place!
...I've decided to dream
a little bigger.
Instead of shrinking and stealing
the monuments of the world
so I could decorate my island,
I'm going to shrink and steal
the cities of the world,
people and all,
so I can have subjects to rule over!
Listen, you're never
going to get away with this!
SMALLS:
Oh, like you're going to stop me!
All right, let's turn her into an ant!
(they laugh)
Here's our chance.
I'll tackle the annoying one,
- you grab the other two.
- Gotcha.
I said I'll tackle the annoying one!
I know, so why are you going
after that one? She's the annoying one.
- Not half as annoying as that one.
- (laughs evilly)
SMALLS: Now, when this machine
gets nice and toasty,
you girls will be shrunk to
the size of dust particles.
Too bad we won't be able to watch,
but we've got a little city to shrink
and steal... called Tokyo.
Maybe you've heard of it. (laughs)
- Now what?
- I can't reach my gadgets.
Look! My laser cutter eyelash curler
shrunk along with me.
This whole time I could have had
great lashes and didn't know it.
- That was close!
- Now we have a city to save!
Strap on your jet-pack backpacks
and let's blow this joint.
Wait up!
There they are
and they're almost ready to go!
Maybe we can destroy
the blimp's steering system
so Smalls can't hold it in position.
How did those annoying little pests
get free?!
That's it!
Hand me the portable Alpha X9!
Watch out! I think he sees us!
(panicked yells)
(laughs)
Yep, he sees us!
We need to split up
or we'll never get close enough.
Cover for me. I'm going in!
(Smalls laughs)
Try this on for size!
- I can't watch.
- Me neither.
That gives me an idea.
OK, we're here. What now?
Follow my lead.
Oh, no!
My jet pack is running out of fuel.
So is mine!
- Really? Mine's fine.
- Alex!
Oops! I mean, oh, no!
I'm out of fuel, too!
We're trapped!
I told you we'd outlast them!
Now this is when the fun really starts.
- SMALLS: Ready?
- BOTH: Aim!
SMALLS: Fire!
(they panic)
You haven't seen the last of me!
Spies, once again, a job well done.
ALL: Thanks, Jerry.
Yo, guys, hello! Can you ease up a bit?
(doorbell)
Good thing I kept my old doll's outfits!
SAM: Hold on, I'll get it.
- This is for...
- CLOVER: Me.
- Yeah... (screams)
- OK, guys, quick!
Shoot me with the gun. I'll have
enough time before Jason shows up
to change from this doll outfit
into my special date outfit.
- Let me do it!
- No, let me!
Oh, my!
Oh, no! I can't wear these!
I can't wear anything!
Jason can't see me like this.
What am I going to do?
Cancel! I'm going to have you
go to the door and cancel my date.
Tell him I'm sick. That I have the flu.
We'll have to reschedule.
Are you sure? I mean,
you could borrow something of ours.
No way, girls. I've been planning
my perfect outfit all week.
- (doorbell)
- Hi, Jason.
- Hi, girls. Is Clover ready?
- She's very sick. Spots everywhere.
She's sorry but she cannot
go out with you today.
(sighs) That was close.
Oops, sorry!
Oh. Hey, Mandy! What's going on?
(gasps) How totally lame!
He's actually falling for that?
Jason, wait! I'm feeling much better!
Those crazy ten minute flus!
I'm glad Clover's back to
her normal self.
I'm not sure "normal"
quite describes it.
Jason! Jaaaasooon!
(they laugh)