♪ Here we go,
we're getting on the road till we stop ♪
♪ And then we'll shop ♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ On a mission undercover
and we're in control ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
Eh, eh, ahem, ladies and gentlemen,
the Bora Bora Resort Hotel
is proud to welcome the recipients
of the Achievements In Science Award.
Enjoy your retreat.
Look!
They're beautiful!
I've never seen anything like that!
SCIENTIST: It's a new species!
They're beautiful! (gasps)
(all scream)
(groans)
(beeping)
What's going on? Where am I?
(evil laughter)
(whirring)
MAN OVER PA SYSTEM:Don't forget,
students, Monday is school picture day.
Let's all try to look our best.
SAM: I am so not ready for picture day!
Tell me about it!
I totally don't know what to wear!
Should I smile this year
or go for the classic pout?
(camera clicks)
Hello, pathetic wannabes.
I'm getting my hair done
by Maurice Maurice,
the greatest stylist in the world.
Only a master such as he
can do justice to my beautiful locks!
(all yawn)
(laughs)
(screams) My hair! Help!
Oh, thank goodness!
Sam, you... you saved my life!
I saved your hair, Mandy.
(screams)
My hair is my life!
I am forever in your debt!
From now on we are friends!
I'll pick you up tonight to go to
that new dance club, best friend.
Uh.. .no, thanks.
No need to thank me.
See you at eight, B.F.
Or we could go to a movie?
Or get something to eat?
How about a latte?
This would be like the best time
to be pulled away to WOOHP!
(all yell)
Sam? Sam?
JERRY: Hello, ladies!
That was perfect timing. Thanks, Jerry.
I have something to show you.
Ten of the world's top scientists
were at a conference in Bora Bora
when something very odd happened.
GIRLS: Bora Bora?!
Hello.
CLOVER: Those are so cute!
SAM: Eww! Those are so gross!
Yes, well those cute gross blobs erased
the scientists' memories completely.
WOOHP needs you to find out
who is behind this and stop them.
This could potentially have
dangerous global ramifications.
Now, let's get your equipment.
JERRY: This is MUCA.
Multi Use Cranium Apparatus.
Everything you need
to sustain yourself underwater.
Cool, do you have one in fuchsia?
Nuclear Powered Jet Boots
for underwater propulsion.
Waist Restrainers containing
titanium grappling hooks,
a repellent spear pistol
and infusion exploders.
And LIAB 9,000.
"Lab In A Briefcase"
for on-the-spot analysis.
And, you'll need to bone up
on your marine biology.
We have to study?
Last but not least, Supercycles.
Voice-activated. Each cycle recognizes
your own particular voice.
Simple commands,
such as "go", "faster", etc.
You tell the bike what to do
and it does it.
Allow me to demonstrate.
JERRY: "Start!"
(engine revving)
GIRLS: Cool!
(chuckles)
They're very sensitive.
GIRLS: Stop!
GIRLS: Wow!
There's no time to lose.
- You must leave right...
- Wait! I can't go!
- Why not?
- I left my new sunglasses at home.
ALEX AND SAM: Clover, please!
You didn't expect me
to go to a tropical island
without my new sunglasses, did you?
Come on, Clover!
Sam-my! Hey, girl!
Ready to hit the dance club?
Uh, Mandy... I can't.
I've got to visit my,
my... uh... sick aunt.
Ew! I hate sick aunts!
But, OK, I can help.
Any relative of yours
is a relative of mine!
No thanks. She's got...uh...
Monkeynucleosis.
Very rare and very contagious.
I wouldn't want you to get it. Gotta go!
Oh!
Now, this is where
the attack took place.
Working undercover
as tourists is the best!
Cool it! We're supposed to be
investigating here!
Who says you can't tan and
investigate at the same time?
Oh!
OH!
Ew! Blob juice!
Don't! That's evidence!
Huh, the blobs aren't organic.
They're man-made.
Somebody manufactured these things!
We'll send this to WOOHP
for further analysis.
Now, let's check out those scientists.
SCIENTIST 1: Who are you?
SCIENTIST 2: Who am I?
SCIENTIST 3: Where am I?
Mommy?
Hi. My name's Clover.
I'm taking biology this year.
When you get your memory back,
you can help me on my mid-term.
Uh, who is biology?
(all scream)
Mr Hannigan, I will only say this once.
One billion dollars must be left
at Black Death Cove
by tomorrow morning at dawn.
If not, I promise you will regret it.
(all gasp)
This is the most horrible thing
I could ever imagine!
Hey, Sam! Hello!
No, that is the most horrible thing
you could ever imagine!
What a totally amazing surprise!
I needed to get a tan for the
school pictures. I look like a mime!
And this is my favorite tanning beach
in the whole world!
- Where's Auntie Monkeynucleosis?
- "Auntie" who?
Oh, oh, yeah! She-she got better.
Great! Now we don't have to
take care of that cranky loon!
We can hang out together cos that's
what best friends are for, right?
So, what exactly are
you all doing here, Sam?
GIRLS: Uh... Um... Well...
The hotel hired us
to give dance lessons!
(dance music)
(Alex cheers)
This is the lamest thing
I have ever seen in my entire life.
(yawns)
Mandy needs her beauty sleep!
Night, Sam.
Meet me at the bazaar tomorrow morning.
We'll go shopping. Just lose the losers!
See ya!
You better get rid of your friend!
She is not my friend!
You know I have a prom coming up...
SAM: Clover! Come on!
(beeping)
OK, we wait here with the money
till somebody shows up.
Just let me know when
the bad guys get here.
- The bad guys are here!
- What?
ALEX: Only two of them?
This should be easy.
Yeah, too easy.
(men gasp)
(grunts)
GIRLS: Run!
(all cough)
- CLOVER: This is so bad for my skin!
- SAM: C'mon, let's get 'em!
- SAM: Go!
- ALEX: Go!
Yeah! Oh, I mean "go"!
(Clover shrieks)
We'll never catch them!
Let's speed it up. Ready?
One, two, three.
GIRLS: Faster!
GIRLS: Super sonic!
(tires squeal)
Hey!
Turn around!
Go the other way!
(Alex screams)
Wow! Hi!
Not you!
(gasps)
(growls)
(horns blare)
ALEX: What the...?
(engines rev)
Wait!
(horns blaring)
There it is!
MAN: Hey!
This chase is over, buddy!
I don't think so!
(screams)
ALEX: Sam!
- Sam!
- Are you all right?
Sam! I've been looking all over for you!
Look at these fabulous things I got!
I am going to look gorgeous in these!
W-who are you?
She got blobbed!
"Blobbed"? Ew! What is going on?
Uh... we were just playing a game!
Yeah! It's called "Who Are You?"
Who are you?!
Sam is really good at it!
I want to play, too!
Uh, sure, you can play the next round,
but you have to play it on jet skis.
Right! Round two is on jet skis.
So, go rent a jet ski
and we'll meet you at the marina!
Jet skis!
- CLOVER: Go!
- ALEX: Ciao!
CLOVER: Go!
(coughs)
Jerry, Sam got hit by a blob
and lost her memory!
Don't let her out of your sight.
She's safest with you.
Listen, I have new information.
We analyzed the blob residue and
traced it to a man named Lester Crowley.
A janitor?
Well, he was a janitor at
The Brooks Marine Biology Institute.
JERRY:He wanted to be a scientist.
He tried some
experimenting on his own.
At night he secretly worked on a cure
for memory loss using sea creatures.
He was discovered, fired and arrested.
He escaped, stealing millions
of dollars worth of equipment.
You need to find him. Fast! Good luck!
Marine biologist wannabe, huh?
I think I know where
we should start looking.
I wish someone would tell me
what is going on!
OK. Your name is Sam.
SAM: "Sam"? Am I a man?
No! You're a girl.
(beeping)
Switch on helmet subs. Down!
CLOVER:You sure these
are made for water landing?
ALEX:Of course they are!
(screaming)
CLOVER:The Lester Crowley
Underwater Research Institute.
- CLOVER:I think this is it!
-SAM:How are we going to get in?
(all scream)
Subtle, no. Effective, yes.
SAM:Hey?What am I supposed to do?
ALEX AND CLOVER:Shh!
SAM: Can I go home, please?
Wherever my home is.
This is not fun at all!
(machines clank)
(beeping)
That's our man!
We will now implement the final phase.
I will unleash my vengeance upon
the world and then... utter chaos.
I will hold the world's
memories in my hand...
We have to sneak back out,
get reinforcements and then...
SAM: Hey! You in the white coat!
Do you know who I am?
Seize them!
Was that a bad thing to do?
You look like intelligent young girls.
I think you'll enjoy a demonstration
of the hatching process
of my blobs, observe.
After hatching, they search
for the closest human brain
and suck the memory out!
I must go, but I do hope you
enjoy the demonstration.
Is this like an initiation into
a secret club or something?
(rumbling)
(all groan)
(all scream)
(growling)
(screams)
(Mandy screams)
Ow! I can't believe I'm saying this
but, "Thanks, Mandy."
What is going on here?
Uh... We're still playing "Who are you?"
Wow! This is a really elaborate game.
Excuse me, but this "game"
is way out of control!
- What about Mandy?
- No time to worry about her.
She's safe below and more importantly,
she's not following us!
(gasps)
(Mandy screams)
Preparing approach to New York City.
(grunting)
CLOVER: Gee, you think he'd have
a bunch of guards in here.
(gasps)
Hey! I was right!
(all scream)
(guards gasp)
(guard screams)
(karate yell)
(laughs)
(grunts and screams)
(screams)
(yells and grunts)
- Gotcha!
- I don't feel so good.
What are you doing here?
Uh, do you have any
of those little bags?
I think I'm gonna barf.
OK, Crowley! It's over!
Turn the plane around!
OK, tell me right now
exactly what is going on!
(screaming)
We've gotta destroy
the rest of those blobs!
If we can jam the machine,
we might be able to.
(grunts)
Can't... reach.. .the switch!
Need something long.
My hair! Sam! Help me!
(Mandy screams)
CLOVER: It's gonna blow!
(screams)
No! No!
(struggling)
Uh, excuse me, spy girls?
I know you're busy tying up
the bad guy and everything,
but who exactly is flying this plane?
(screaming)
Hey! What about me? Help!
(explosion)
OK, I saved you, but I do not
want you as my best friend! Got it?
(groans)
OK, Crowley,
we gotta restore Sam's memory.
Where's the thingy
with all the memories?
(growls)
Huh?
- Sam, do you know who you are?
- Duh! I'm Sam.
We're spies for the World Organization
of Human Protection, ya know, WOOHP.
You two look tired.
Yeah, well, it's been
kind of a long day!
ALEX: You're back!
So, have we found out who's behind this?
Did WOOHP get anything
from the blob residue?
(laughs)
Hi, Mandy. Did we...?
What is she doing up here?
Oh, oh my! My gosh! You're all spies!
I cannot wait to tell everyone
about this at school!
- Girls, we've got a problem here.
- I don't think so.
(Mandy screams)
I'm glad we erased the part
of Mandy's memory
so she doesn't remember
we're you-know-whats.
Yeah. It's so great to have
the old Mandy back!
Why are you girls even bothering
to get your pictures taken?
You'll never look as gorgeous as me!
Are my perfect teeth in focus?
Hey, Monkey Boy,
you are shooting perfection here!
Work with me!
MANDY: I knew I should have brought
my own photographer!
GIRLS: Cheese!