♪Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop♪
♪And then we'll shop♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪On a mission undercover
and we're in control♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪Here we go♪
And how may I help you?
Let's see. Well, for starters,
you can hand over all the cash
you got in this dump.
Nobody move!
(coughing)
ALL:Cheese!
(school bell rings)
- Ta-da!
- (both gasp)
- So, what do you think?
- Well, your outfit is very... bright.
I'm hoping it'll remind that hot new
transfer student of his homeland.
- Where's he from again?
- Texas.
OK, here goes.
So, Billy Bob.
If you're not too busy tomorrow night,
maybe you'd like to go line dancing
with me. Beverly Hills style, that is.
Well, that's mighty hospitable of you,
Mandy. I'd love to.
Great.
I'll pick you up at eight o'clock.
How dare you steal my look!
Please. I was into Texas way before you.
Yeah! Mandy practically invented
the rhinestone.
Totally.
Besides, Billy's made up his mind.
(screams)
That girl is a fashion thief and she is
not going to get away with this.
- What the...
- (all scream)
Terrific! The last thing I need right
now is another...
..stupid WOOHP spy mission!
(all gasp)
- Ouch!
- What's this all about, Jerry?
I think you girls know
what this is all about.
ALL:Cheese!
Is this some kind of sick joke?
That's not us robbing that bank.
I am very disappointed in you girls.
(sighs)
Throw these girls into
the electromagnetic holding tank
until we can reprogram them.
What do you mean, "reprogram"?
We're going to implant Behavioral
Modification Chips into your brains.
You'll never have another
aggressive thought as long as you live.
- No, you guys, don't!
- Get your hands off me!
CLOVER: Jerry, help us!
Sorry, girls. It's out of my hands.
ALEX: These gaudy electromagnetic
boots are so cyber-repulsive.
Not as repulsive as getting microchips
implanted into our skulls.
We gotta bust out and find those cheap
knock-off bank robbers
so we can clear our names.
(scoffs) Good luck.
Hang on. I've got a plan.
CLOVER: Hey, what gives?
(screams)
Wow, you short-circuited the boots!
I can move my feet again.
SAM: Great, but we're still stuck
in this cell.
- Not for long.
- (shrieks)
Huh?
CLOVER: Bet Mandy's shoes
wouldn't do that.
They're escaping. Code nine! Code nine!
(alarm blares)
JERRY:Grab them so I can implant
the microchips into their skulls.
SAM: In here!
Quick. Grab whatever you can. We're
gonna need all the help we can get.
Yeah!
(all shriek)
Just relax, girls.
It'll all be over with soon.
Now!
CLOVER: How are we gonna lose them?
SAM: Time to fly, girls.
How do I make this thing go?
I can't even set my digital watch.
CLOVER: Just do something!
(all scream)
(they gasp)
ALL: Whoa!
I can't believe Jerry almost
microwaved my brain.
We'd better get out of the air.
We stick out like a sore thumb.
Put it down next to that warehouse.
I said NEXT to the warehouse.
Something reeks here,
and I don't mean Alex's flying skills.
SAM: Oh, gross! There's our culprit.
Whoa! Look, my hairclip is actually
a high-tech frisbee.
That's no frisbee.
It's a mini-satellite.
We can use this to link
to WOOHP's computer system.
Maybe we can get a closer look
at the footage Jerry showed us.
We're in.
Wait, go back.
Watch the Clover imposter.
CLOVER: She left a shred of my shirt...
uh, I mean, her shirt on that cactus.
Maybe it's still there.
Too bad we're not allowed in that bank.
Maybe there's a way to get inside
the bank without raising suspicion.
CLOVER: So much
for not raising suspicions.
SAM: Just act confident.
ALEX: That's easy for you to say.
You're not dressed like a waiter.
SAM: You're not a waiter, you're our
driver. Just look for the shirt piece.
MAN: Hello, sir, madam.
Can I help you with something?
Oh, we're just looking
at your lovely financial place
to decide if we want to deposit
all of our... stocks
and... municipal... things here.
You look very familiar.
Have we met before?
Uh, that would be quite impossible.
You see, we just moved here
from... Swedenavia.
Swedenavia?
Oh, yes. Very small country. Very cold.
Yes! I found it!
Found what? I'm sorry, found what?
Oh, our driver seems to have found...
the lost keys to our limo.
Yes, we simply must be going now.
The country club awaits. Ta-ta.
Sir, you forgot your... mustache?
Wait a second.
They were the bank robbers!
This is weird.
It almost feels like... flesh.
SAM: Look. The fabric contains
traces of human DNA!
No wonder it feels like flesh.
Why would someone wear a shirt
made out of flesh?
I can't imagine that would breathe
very well in warm weather.
Look, she didn't rip her shirt.
She ripped her... skin.
- Ew.
- There's something else here. Writing.
SAM: "Replatech Industries"?
What does that mean?
Let's check out the WOOHP database.
Apparently they're the medical lab
that created this creepy material.
I think it's time we pay Replatech
a visit. Uh, I'll drive.
I'd better cloak the Heli-Jet so we can
make a stealthy landing on the roof.
(all scream)
Oopsy.
ALEX: Wow! Now, that's impressive.
Check it out. Some sort of force field.
SAM: Whatever it is,
those birds didn't set off the alarms.
It must be set to detect any metal
that breaks its field.
How are we going to investigate the
building without giving ourselves away?
Why do I always get the cruddy jobs?
SAM:We're getting a picture.
OK, ew! What is that?
It looks like someone's farming humans.
(screams) Bring me up!
Bring me up!
What's wrong with Alex?
(both scream)
We got company.
ALEX:Hello?
Girl on a rope down here! Pull me up!
(screams)
Need a lift?
No. I need a barf bag!
Phew! That was close.
Close?! Hello, in case no one noticed,
I just got tossed around
like a human yo-yo.
Not to mention getting grabbed by...
What's this?
- Looks like a fingernail.
- I have a hunch.
Use the Compowder
to check its composition.
It's made of the same substance
as the skin we found. But get this.
- The DNA matches Clover's DNA.
- OK, no way!
I wouldn't be caught dead wearing
that cheesy sea foam nail polish.
ALL: The intruders have escaped, sir.
MAN: So, the spies are on to me.
I underestimated them.
It won't happen again.
So what's the connection between
the DNA, the robbery and Replatech?
I don't know,
but I hope we figure it out soon.
The prospect of spending another minute
in this warehouse is...
(crashing)
WOOHP must have tracked us.
Give it up, girls.
We have the place surrounded.
Scatter, quick!
Keep a tight perimeter.
Don't let them get away.
(sighs) What the...
- Psst!
- Huh?
Sammy, you made it.
Have you seen Clover?
Right here.
Are you feeling alright?
- Of course.
- What now?
We have to get back to Replatech
and figure out what is going on
before Jerry turns us into vegetables.
But how are we going to break
into Replatech?
That place has tighter security
than Fort Knox.
(helicopter whirrs)
I can get us in.
I mean, I think I saw
a secret entrance in the forest.
OK. It's worth a shot.
How are we going to get back
to the island?
The Heli-Jet is swarming
with WOOHP agents.
Leave it to me.
They must have slipped past us.
Pull our agents out.
(both gasp)
Where is my jet?
You don't think Jerry will miss this,
do you?
Oh, Clover, it looks like
you chipped your nail.
Must have happened
when the warehouse collapsed.
ALEX: What exactly are we looking for?
I know I spotted some sort of hidden
entrance around here somewhere.
I don't know how you could've spotted
anything in this dense forest.
(all scream)
OK, so I guess you were right
about the secret entrance.
Hey, wait a second.
You said you wouldn't be caught dead
wearing cheesy sea foam nail polish.
That's ridiculous.
I love sea foam nail polish!
Love it! Sea foam! Sea foam!
Sea foam! Love it! Sea foam!
OK, take it easy. I like sea foam too.
(gasps) What the...?
Let me go, you phony!
Who... What are you?
MAN: Impressive, aren't they?
I made them myself.
Nurtured them since they were
little more than strands of DNA.
Incredible likeness, don't you think?
And to think that Clover was upset
when Mandy stole her look.
Now that's really stealing her look.
Wait a second. You look familiar.
(screams)
Macker the safecracker.
It took my hair a year to grow back
after that mission.
As you can see,
that fall took its toll on me.
After I escaped from prison, I created
those clones using DNA from your hair.
Now I will destroy your lives
the way you tried to destroy mine.
I will now use my army of clones
to rob the central bank in every country
in the world at the exact same moment.
Of course, everyone will think
you girls perpetrated the crimes.
Like you'll actually get away with that.
Watch me! To your planes, girls!
If you'll excuse me, I must get
to my command center in the Alps.
Take them away.
Clover, you're alive!
Yeah, me
and 100 cheap knock-off Clovers.
Did you see those things up there?
Totally. That's why we've got
to get out of here and stop Macker.
But how?
No!
Good thing I decided to go
with diamond tipped spurs after all.
Let's get to the Alps
before it's too late.
SAM: There's Macker.
Looks like he's using the transmitter
to control the clones.
ALEX: How are we going to take out
the transmitter?
We'll have to figure something out fast.
It's already started.
Get into position, ladies.
It's almost time.
CLOVER: OK, so maybe you have our looks.
Let's see if you have our moves.
- Yay!
- (clones scream)
(screams) Ouch!
Phew.
Now is the time, girls.
What's going on?
Why aren't you robbing the banks?
What do you think
you're doing to my beloved clones?
Ow! Let go of my hair!
(sighs)
(helicopter whirrs)
JERRY: Girls! Girls, wait!
(both scream)
SAM: Get away from us, Jerry!
Girls, it's OK.
We realize that you were
only trying to clear your names.
Oh, I guess we're lucky you figured
it out before you gave us lobotomies.
I hope you girls will accept
my sincerest apology.
ALL: Apology?
You'll be collecting your pension by the
time you're done making this up to us.
Snowball! Girls, please, sorry!
Now that we've taken care
of those clones,
it's time to win back Billy Bob and
expose Mandy for the thief that she is.
"Thief?"
Don't you think that's kind of harsh?
Well, that's what she is.
But she won't have a chance
to steal this new outfit.
Um, I don't know how to break this
to you, Clover, but...
Oh, poo! That must be
where I got my design ideas.
I guess Mandy's not a thief after all.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I think I owe her an apology.
You thief!
- Billy Bob?
- Oh, hey, girls.
I'd like you to meet my new steady gal,
Alpha. Isn't she so original?
Steady gal? But Billy Bob,
I just designed this new outfit for you.
Oh, well, honestly, I never really liked
that whole cowgirl look.
That's why I left Texas.
- This is so your fault!
- You need to hire a new stylist.
(both argue at once)