♪Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop♪
♪And then we'll shop♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go ♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪On a mission undercover
and we're in control♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪Here we go♪
(photographers shout encouragement)
(models scream)
Clover, where are you taking us?
SAM: Last time she did this we ended up
at the Body-Piercing Hut, remember?
That's right! It took us four hours
to convince her that a lip ring
wouldn't "enhance her natural beauty."
Relax, girls,
this surprise is totally piercing free.
Now take off your blindfolds.
Ta-da!
The Groovy Smoothie Shack?
I don't get it, Clover.
Are you thirsty or something?
No. I'm here to sign up for the
Miss Groovy Smoothie beauty contest
- and you're here to support me.
- A food court beauty contest?
You're kidding, right? I mean,
you know beauty's only skin deep.
Of course. I'm not kidding!
And, judging by the competition,
- I'd say I'm a shoe-in for victory.
- Um, not so fast, Clover.
This is my competition and mine alone.
Nothing or no-one is gonna stop me from
becoming Miss Groovy Smoothie
and launching my modeling career.
(laughs)
- Is that a fact?
- Yes, it is.
Cos everyone who's ever won this contest
has gone on to bigger and better things.
And I intend to join them,
thank you very much.
Now, why don't you and those cheap shoes
of yours just step off.
The only thing that's cheap around
is here is your pathetic attempt
at trying to get me to back down.
Now outta my way!
Come on, girls.
Let's go plan my victory party.
(Mandy scoffs)
MANDY: As if!
Can you believe the nerve of that girl?
Tell me about it. I mean, how dare she
accuse you of wearing cut-rate shoes!
I say we ditch the mall,
grab a mani/pedi,
- and forget all about boring old Mandy.
- BOTH: Deal!
(they scream)
(elevator dings)
(groans)
I don't remember the parking structure
being quite this dark.
Uh, Alex, something tells me
we're not at the mall anymore.
(they scream)
- Hello, ladies.
- Jerry. Should have known.
Nice to see you too. Now, allow me
to brief you about your new mission.
- So much for that mani/pedi.
- We've just been informed
that approximately a dozen models
from all over the world
have literally been stolen
within the last 24 hours.
- What do you mean "stolen?"
- We're currently en route to New York
where you'll go undercover
as journalists at Fashion Week,
a hugely important industry event
where you'll have access to
everyone who's anyone.
You want us to see what we
can find out about the abductions?
Precisely. And now for the gadgets.
This time you'll be utilizing
the magnetic spring-loaded
bungee belt in faux snakeskin,
the ultra-inflatable nylon tek vest,
a pair of hologram-projecting
mood rings,
the titanium drill-heel boot
for impromptu tunneling,
and last, but not least,
the M-Ray contact lens in aquamarine.
- "M-Ray?"
- For seeing through metal.
Now, goodbye and good luck, spies.
I'll be in touch!
(they scream)
I've heard of fashion police,
but this is ridiculous.
Must be because of the abductions.
Man, talk about a mob scene!
Everyone's here to see the new modeling
phenom, Gazelle.
- Gazelle?
- She arrived on the scene overnight.
The witch is already getting
all the available modeling work.
Me and the rest of the supermodels
are pretty much out of luck.
I think we need a better view.
(crowd clamors)
CLOVER: I've never seen anyone so...
so perfect. It's unbelievable!
- Better keep an eye on her, Alex.
- Right.
- What's she doing?
- Taking off her gloves.
- ALEX: Hmm... now that's odd.
- What?
The skin on her arms and hands...
it's all sorts of different colors.
As in her tanning bed's on the fritz?
"Different colors" as in
the Bride of Frankenstein.
Maybe she's not so perfect after all.
How about we go backstage
for a closer look?
Now remember, we're supposed to be
journalists so act professional.
CLOVER: Ew! Nast!
Not exactly the professional demeanor
I had in mind, Clover.
Hi, Gazelle. I'm Sam from
Trend Of The Momentmagazine.
I wanted to tell you
how much I enjoyed the show.
Thanks. But the truth is I owe
everything to my agency.
Really. I wouldn't exist without them.
MAN: Yes,
and we wouldn't exist without her.
I'm Helmet from Picture Perfect.
I represent Gazelle.
She's single-handedly
put our agency on the map.
- You're a modeling agent?
- That's right.
So you'd know if I had
what it takes to be a model?
- (sighs)
- (groans)
My philosophy is that everyone has
something about them that's perfect.
In your case, it's your legs.
So, you're saying I'm model material?!
Sorry. Not quite.
Come on, Gazelle.
You need your beauty rest.
Gazelle, wait! You dropped your...
(gasps) ...ear?
I've sent the ear to WOOHP for analysis.
Our next move is to investigate
Picture Perfect.
Picture Perfect, please.
I mean, what kind of pathetic agency
are they, anyway?
Take that Helmet guy, for instance.
He calls himself an agent?
He wouldn't know a model
if she sashayed right into him!
Come again?
No matter what Helmet says,
I know I'm model material.
- (knocking)
- MAN: Special delivery.
It's from the Groovy Smoothie Shack.
It says I'm a finalist in the
Miss Groovy Smoothie beauty contest!
This proves it, I am model material!
(they sigh)
- Ouch!
- Are you OK?
I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
We wouldn't want anything to happen
to our potential beauty queen.
(helicopter whirrs)
(screams)
Clover!
CLOVER: Hey!
You're stretching out my perfect legs!
ALEX: They're trying to shake us off!
(they scream)
OK, that was a little too close
for comfort.
Speaking of comfort,
you wanna get me out of this thing?
CLOVER: Help me!
Quick. Look inside the helicopter
and see if there's any clues!
ALEX: The pilot has the Picture Perfect
logo on his jacket!
We'd better call Jerry.
Hello, ladies. How's the Big Apple?
Rotten, Jerry. Clover's been kidnapped.
Oh, dear.
That's the second time this month.
What do you know about
the Picture Perfect Modeling Agency?
JERRY:Let's see... apparently it's run
by an ex-model named Tuesday Tate.
Their headquarters are in
Sydney, Australia.
SAM: We're journalists from
Trend Of The Moment.
You aren't on Miss Tate's schedule.
You'll have to leave.
Is it me or is there something
very familiar about that woman?
Not to mention something very rude.
Looks like we're gonna have to enter
Picture Perfect the hard way.
SAM: Never underestimate
the power of a good accessory.
ALEX: Looks more like some kind of
high-tech clinic than a modeling agency.
(they gasp)
SAM: I wonder what's in here?
Hey, check that out!
Those are both Gazelle?
Man, talk about a split personality.
Jackpot! Gazelle's "donors."
Stacey, Aimee, Anna, Kelley, Gretchen...
- (Compowder alert)
- Sam here.
Hello, ladies.
I thought you'd be interested to know
that the ear you sent me belongs to
a model who was abducted last week.
Her name is Gretchen.
(gasps) Sam, that's... that's one of
the names on the donor list!
Donor list?
I know what it seems like, Alex,
but how could it be possible?
(woman clears throat)
Can I help you, ladies?
Uh, yes. Yes, you can. We're journalists
fromTrend Of The Momentand...
...and we're here to interview you!
OK. But you'll have to make it snappy.
I'm leaving soon for a model search
in New Zealand.
So... I hear that you used to be
a model, Miss Tate. Why did you quit?
I injured my leg at a photo shoot
two years ago.
It was a circus theme and
I was to play the role of lion tamer.
Unfortunately, the lion tamed me.
Now I have this.
Why don't you tell us about
Picture Perfect
and how it is that you've achieved
this sudden success?
- (telephone rings)
- Tuesday speaking.
Oh, I see...
Would you ladies mind moving to
the waiting room down the hall
while I take this call?
- Not at all.
- No problem.
Those two are definitely trouble.
Well, then, we'd better eliminate them.
- (alarm blares)
- SPIES: Uh-oh.
I'd say our interview's
just been cut short!
We'd better find Clover
before it's too late.
Get them!
(growls)
We have to get to that restricted area
we found earlier.
It's gotta be around here somewhere.
(they scream)
- SAM: Clover!
- What happened to you?
Picture Perfect steals body parts!
That's how they created Gazelle!
Right now there's someone else out there
running around with my perfect legs!
(they gasp)
Don't worry.
We're gonna get all of you out of here.
TATE: I wouldn't be so sure about that.
We can't just let you leave
and risk you telling the world
about our little secret.
- (they struggle)
- Why are you doing this?
It's simple, really. I want to create
an army of perfect models
so that I can dominate the industry
that destroyed my career.
Couldn't you just steal yourself
a new leg instead?
I mean,
it seems like a lot less trouble.
You've got a point. But somehow my evil
revenge plan just sounds like more fun.
Well, it'll never work.
Perhaps you'll feel a little differently
after my demonstration, darling.
Hey, those are my legs!
Correction. They were your legs.
Now they belong to Picture Perfect.
Just like your friends' body parts
are about to.
Prepare to be modelized.
(beeping)
(they shriek)
(gasps)
And I thought I had it bad.
Now, since I'll be getting plenty of new
donors from all around the world
at the Auckland Convention Center,
I'm quite ready to dispose of you.
- Dispose of us?
- Yes.
We're gonna dump you in the ocean
where you'll join a school of ferocious,
man-eating sharks for lunch.
(they shriek)
I don't know about you girls, but I'm
not ready to be fish food quite yet.
Me neither. Even if I do look
like a science experiment gone bad.
Trust me.
We'll be outta here in no time.
CLOVER: Fine. I'll trust you.
Just promise me you'll stop smiling.
Your braces are blinding me.
Nice goin', Sam. What's our next move?
Since we can't get into the cockpit,
I'll get the pilot to come to us.
Just be ready for him.
(yells)
- Good work, Red.
- Right back at ya.
Now all we have to do is get to
New Zealand and stop Tuesday.
SAM: That's a great idea,
except for one thing.
Now that you've knocked the pilot
unconscious, who'll fly the plane?
- (they gasp)
- OK, why am I doing this?
Because the pedals
are really hard to press
and you're the one with the...
stout, powerful legs.
Right.
HELMET: Oh, that skin, it's magnificent.
We can definitely use you.
I'd say your toes are among
the loveliest specimens I've ever seen.
You're Picture Perfect material
for sure.
Now why don't you step inside the
Modelizer...
I mean, the photo booth...
so we can take some pictures of you?
That should be plenty.
In a matter of minutes
we'll have ourselves
an army of Picture Perfect models.
(they shriek)
- (airplane engine)
- What the...?
(they scream)
- SAM: Way to go, Clover!
- All in a day's work.
Uh, guys... I think we've got trouble.
We've got to get them out of
the Modelizer
before they end up pieced together
like us!
It's locked!
Don't worry.
I'll find Tuesday and her key.
She's on the other side of
the convention center with Helmet!
Well, then, we'd better get moving.
ALEX: Gotcha!
Now hand over the key
to the modelizing machine!
You want the key? Go get it!
Great. This is gonna be like trying
to find a nail file in a haystack.
Well, you'd better hurry because once
the modelizing process is complete,
it'll be irreversible. Just a new
feature I've added to the machine.
What are you doing?
Trying to locate the key with the
compowder fingerprint scanner.
Bingo! Now let's get back to the girls!
What about these two?
JERRY: Don't worry.
We'll take care of them.
ALEX: So... you're sure about this?
You're definitely dropping out?
Absolutely. I've decided that
I've had enough modeling
and beauty contests for one lifetime.
The whole scene's just way too evil.
Besides, ever since I got my legs back,
I remember how gorgeous I truly am.
I don't need anyone else's validation.
I always knew you were
beautiful and smart.
JUDGE: Well, that's too bad
because you would have won.
But since you dropped out,
I'll be awarding the first runner up
your $25,000 cash
and your brand new convertible
sportscar. Congratulations, Mandy!
Thank you! Thank you one and all!
CLOVER: $25,000?
Wait, I was only kidding!
It was a joke!
I want to be Miss Groovy Smoothie!
Oh, well. So much for Clover
thinking the whole scene is evil.