♪Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop♪
♪And then we'll shop♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪On a mission undercover
and we're in control♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪Here we go♪
Oh!
Out of the way!
Grandpa here lost his nerve.
Come on, I'm psyched to see
how fast this thing is!
LOUDSPEAKER:Let's see how you like
getting pushed around, Bret!
Hey, what's up with this?
(screams)
LOUDSPEAKER:Bret has been a bad boy.
Bret needs a lesson.
Sam, Alex, this Court has no choice
but to find you guilty of
violating the school dress code.
But Clov... your Honor,
our heels are only a half-inch higher
than the code allows.
Can't you give us a break?
Well, considering the circumstances,
I guess I can let you off with
a suspended sentence.
- Objection, Your Dis-Honor!
- (screams)
This is total favoritism!
I agree. You're much too lenient
to be a student court judge, Clover.
I'm replacing you with Mandy.
Thank you, Ms Brooks. I promise
I'll restore dignity to this cour...
And I'll restore integrity, too.
This court finds all three of you
in contempt,
and sentences you to three weeks
of picking up trash!
Next case!
ALL: What?!
"Integrity?" Ha! What a brown-noser!
Yeah! Who's she think she is,
the Supreme Court?
Ew! This is, like, supremely nasty!
There must be a way
to pick this stuff up faster.
There is, check it out!
(all scream)
Can't you get a normal office?
Sorry, ladies, but we need you urgently.
14 hours ago, a computer trapped
a student named Bret Brinkley
on a Las Vegas rollercoaster.
(Bret sobs)
We've had two similar attacks.
In Italy, a tourist was attacked by
an airport baggage machine.
And a computerized elevator
at Silicon Valley High
left the principal quite shook-up.
(principal grunts)
Yikes. More proof
that climbing stairs is healthier.
Your first stop is Las Vegas.
Today's gadgets menu includes
decoy purse, life raft, parachute...
Don't spray on that perfume.
It's liquid nitrogen. It freezes
steel, makes it as brittle as glass.
Extremely cool!
Careful, the hairdryer is
an infrared heat-ray.
The stereo is a sonic disintegrator
and the camera fires a laser beam.
- (gasps)
- Guess I won't need film, will I?
(Bret screams)
Looks like Bret's had enough fun,
get ready to grab him!
Careful, here he comes. Go time!
(Bret screams)
(screams)
Come on, pal,
time to give someone else a turn.
Remind me to stick to the merry-go-round
next time we go to an amusement park.
(sobbing) Thank you!
I don't get it. How could
a computer voice know your name?
Search me.
I'm on the football team, babe.
I don't study computers,
or anything else.
- Football?
- Yeah. I bet you ace all your tests.
I don't have to, babe.
I just grab the nearest nerd
and, uh, "persuade" him to help me.
Speaking as a nerd, I'm starting to see
why computers attack you.
What do you mean, computers?
You talk like there's more than one.
In case you haven't noticed,
this hotel is holding
the annual computerized gadget show.
(all scream)
Why are they coming at me like that?
COMPUTER VOICE:Naughty, naughty, Bret.
Your punishment isn't over!
OK, say cheese.
Oopsie, wrong camera.
Get out of the way!
- Bret has been a bad boy...
-(screams)
-Bret needs a lesson!
- Time for you to split, honey!
SAM: There's never an energy crisis
when you need one!
Bret has been a bad boy!
OK, who's next?
Chill, Alex. You got 'em all.
It's like those computers knew Bret,
we gotta get him somewhere safe.
I'll have WOOHP agents pick him up.
We have to get to Italy, before
anything else happens to that gym coach.
(gasps)
Oh, you want some, Mr Machine?
Victim number two, Coach Joe Hassler
has been laying low here
on the Isle of Capri
ever since he got baggage-handled.
Look, I've never been to Vegas,
I don't know this Bret kid
and I don't wanna go anywhere.
You'll be safer at WOOHP.
But cars, planes, ships,
they all have computer chips now!
If computers are out to get me,
how do I travel?
SPIES: Hmm...
Hey! This is what I call low-tech.
This funicular railway is powered by
a cable. No computer on board.
(all yell)
Uh, Sam, does that go for the
cable motors down in the station?
I'm guessing the answer is no!
COMPUTER VOICE:You've been a bad
boy, Coach. Time for your punishment!
(coach yells)
COACH: Help!
Look out!
(man yells)
- The brake lever is jammed!
- Oh, we are so dead!
We can still trip the brake if we
climb outside to reach the wheel.
Like I said, we're dead!
Clover!
- OK, time for plan B!
- Do we even have a Plan B?
We do now. It's called... jump!
(loud crash)
This may be a dumb question to ask a
gym coach, but do you have any enemies?
- Only every kid I ever taught.
- Any who were good with computers?
Well, I had this one geek running laps
all last year. I forgot his name.
He transferred to Silicon Valley.
Silicon Valley High? Isn't that
where victim number three is principal?
That's it! The coach picks on kids
at one school, Bret at another.
What if they both bullied the same
kid who's now at Silicon Valley? Mm...
Time to pay a visit to
Silicon Valley High.
We can drop the coach off
at WOOHP on the way.
(men groan)
(all yell)
(groans) Every time I think
Jerry can't come up with
a more annoying way for us to travel,
he outdoes himself.
Wow... Silicon Valley High makes
our school look so...
So 20th Century.
How can we blend in
so we don't look so suspicious?
By not blending in. Let's take
a backstage tour of their auditorium.
Wow, look at all that!
Yeah!
Uh, sorry,
Principal Veegun is out sick today.
(English accent)
Oh, dear. Can you 'elp us, luv?
We're new exchange students!
I'm Samantha, from England.
Alexandra from Russia.
Is enrolling in school we want.
I am Cloverpatra, from Egypt.
Hi, I'm Adam Lewis.
Those clothes look familiar.
You've never, uh,
done a school play here, have you?
- Nyit. We are just arriving.
- (giggles)
A thousand pardons, effendi. We wish to
meet other students who are new here.
Could we see your, how you say,
database of new arrivals?
Sure, let me input my password.
Just don't tell the principal, OK?
"CHAD?"
CHAD stands for Computer Home Analyzer
and Defender. My invention.
He... it... can access
any computer anywhere.
I spend a lot of time on CHAD
cos Dad's always moving us.
I guess we both know how hard it is to
make friends when you're new in school.
All those bullies and snobs...
(normal accent) Yeah, sure.
(Egyptian accent)
Excuse me, I am busy.
Adam! I warned you about using
my computer to download games
or whatever it is you do!
I'm revoking your access permanently.
What?! But Principal Veegun,
you can't do that!
No? Watch me. Now get out!
And would you three explain?
Mrs Veegun, you shouldn't have
come back. You're in huge danger!
Danger? From whom?
Aw, man, I can't play with the school
mainframe anymore, CHAD!
Don't worry, Adam. I already
uploaded instructions to it.
Vera Veegun won't bother us again.
(door slams)
Are your door locks computerized?
Yes. Windows, too. Why do you ask?
(shutters slam / all scream)
And your sprinklers!
Hey, CHAD? What's going on?
Just a little prank, Adam.
I'll show you when we get home.
Sam! I left my laser camera backstage
when I changed clothes!
Oh, no! And I left the boom-box!
Wait, I've still got my fanny pack.
CHAD:You've been a bad girl, Vera.
Now I have to punish you!
There's that creepy voice
that loves to dish out punishment.
You're worried about a copier?
No, I'm worried about its stapler!
- (gasps)
- How long can you keep that up?
Won't need to for long,
in a minute we're gonna run out of air.
Sam, give me your pack!
Hang on, we're hitting white water!
(all scream)
You OK?
I'm going to the faculty lounge.
I just need to faint for a while.
Ten students transferred here.
And one was Adam.
But could any kid hack into
so many systems, so fast?
It's not humanly possible.
Wait a sec, that voice we keep
hearing doesn't sound human.
Maybe our hacker isn't human!
Jerry, we have ten suspects,
but if you run a check on...
Later, Sam. Someone in Silicon Valley
just used the Internet
to hack into a missile base on Guam.
I'll send a jet to pick you up.
Sergeant Clover, relieving you, sir.
General wishes to see you
on the double, sir.
We gotta stop those missiles!
Get back!
(screams)
Uh-oh. I've seen that password before.
Sorry, girls, you're not
going to interfere this time.
Excuse me now,
I have some schools to vaporize.
(gasps) We're running out of time!
Oops, did I mess that up for you?
SPIES: Yeah!
Clever. But all you've done is
buy a few hours.
I'll just infiltrate another silo.
And you're not going anywhere.
Where's that instant metal freezer?
Let's get back to Silicon Valley.
The only way to stop this,
is to find that hacker.
Our suspects narrowed to one.
Adam's password is
the name of his invention, "CHAD."
- (computer bleeps)
- What are you running?
Oh, I ran those so-called exchange
students through some databases.
You mean Samantha,
Alexandra and...
I mean Sam, Alex and Clover.
They're from Beverly Hills High.
Those liars!
CHAD, I want you to mess
their grades up so bad
- they get put back in kindergarten!
-No problem.
Put on my virtual reality helmet
and you can see all our latest pranks.
Wait a sec, I asked you to
prank everyone, but...
...you've been hurting them instead!
Coach Hassler
and Principal Veegun and Bret.
Yes, the ones who hurt us.
They've been bad...
they must be punished.
And now you're... you're gonna
fire missiles at all my old schools?!
You wished they could be destroyed.
All those bullies and snobs.
But I was mad when I said that! I just
wanted to prank everyone, not hurt them!
CHAD:
No. We're in this together now, Adam.
We need to share your mind,
your creativity, your body.
You're right, CHAD. Combined with your
power, nothing on Earth can stop us.
Target those schools
and prepare for countdown.
No one picked up. The message says
his father is out of town.
- You think Adam's setting a trap?
- Not Adam. That thing he invented.
You said it yourself, Alex,
the hacker is too fast to be human.
It travels on the Internet, controls
other computers... That's the answer!
CHAD thinks for itself!
An evil computer with a mind of its own?
That is so creepy.
SPIES: Whoa!
We have to pull CHAD's plug.
A t the source. We all set?
Adam programmed CHAD for home defense.
So, think stealth.
Yee-hah!
SAM: Whoa!
(klaxon alarm blares)
Busted!
- Look out!
- (mechanical barking)
Launching purse decoy!
(growling)
(mechanical snarl)
(mechanical barking)
(all gasp)
CLOVER: The heck with stealth. (yells)
Stage two intruders.
Initiate arctic defense..
(whooshing)
Not exactly a warm welcome!
I bet that's Adam's room!
(both scream)
(screams)
Finally, the silos are open.
Locked on to target-schools.
(gasps) CHAD's launching missiles
at Adam's schools!
Ten seconds to ignition... nine...
SAM: Adam, are you in there?
- CHAD:Eight...
- (crash)
Those girls have been bad.
They must be punished. Seven...
(all scream)
Aim for the power cord!
Yeah! Huh?
Sorry, girls, we have
a back-up generator. Six...
This vacuum... really sucks!
Adam, help us!
Huh? What? Can't hear you...
CHAD:Five...
Yes, you can! Use your will power!
You can't let CHAD win!
CHAD:Tisk-tisk. Four...
So, you're trying to betray me, Adam?
Very well. I'll retarget
the missiles to this house.
And upload myself to a new computer
at the Pentagon. Two...
One... zero!
(spies struggle)
(air whistles)
(grunts)
(both) Yeah!
Too little, too late. And now, farew...
Adam, you shorted out my uplink.
Come on, we got about ten seconds!
Adam, you can't abandon me.
I order you to come back... stop...
What have I done? I made a monster
who almost destroyed us all.
You didn't know what CHAD was doing.
I was just scared
you wouldn't snap out of it.
You think that was scary? In a few
hours, we have to face Judge Mandy.
(groans)
OK, whoa! This is contempt of court!
Mandy, enough is enough.
Tell me about it. I'll sentence them
to six weeks picking up trash.
No, you won't. You have utterly failed
to enforce the dress code.
You are off the student court!
Oh, really? Well, if I'm not judge
anymore, then I demand a new job!
Mandy, you missed a milk carton.
(growls)
(squeals)
Sour milk! Run!
(groans)