♪ Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop ♪
♪ And then we'll shop ♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby
Here we go, go, go ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ On a mission undercover
and we're in control ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
(alarm blaring)
(screaming)
- (bell rings)
- Fire!
(imitates sirens)
Fire! Fire!
(school bell ringing)
- SAM: No way.
- CLOVER: Way.
- SAM: So then what'd you do?
- CLOVER: The only thing I could.
- SAM: No way.
- Way!
- You're so cool.
- (horn blares)
(Clover gasps)
Wow.
ALEX: What is it, Clover?
- Yeah, are you OK?
- I'm more than OK.
- I'm in love.
- Ew! Caitlin's brother?
We really have to get her a blindfold.
Why hello, Rick. So good to see you.
Hey, Clover.
How would you love
to give me a ride home?
Ah, I can't. Gotta go to the mall.
Nice skirt. Where'd you get that?
- (giggles)
- I gotta get my kid sister a present.
CLOVER: Kid sister?
I bet his kid sister
wouldn't wear something like this.
My mom wouldn't wear
something like that.
Maybe you should just be yourself,
Clover.
Be myself? Hello?! Rick's a senior.
As in, he's used to sophisticated women.
Yeah, but if a person doesn't like you
for who you are...
You guys, we're in the spy business.
Reinventing ourselves is what we do.
(all gasp)
(all scream)
(all grunt)
Girls, we have
a worldwide problem on our hands.
Vital members of society
have stopped doing their jobs.
They're only interested
in playing with toys.
- ALEX: Toys?
- You're kidding, right?
- Unfortunately, I'm quite serious.
- Whoa.
This chaos will turn into pandemonium
unless we nip it in the bud.
And so, your mission is
to go undercover as buyers.
Finally. A mission I can relate to.
As we speak,
there's a toy fair in Taiwan.
Perhaps you can find a clue there as
to who's behind this bizarre phenomenon.
I've assembled some gadgets for you.
There's the Magne-Belt.
Yeah, that's a little too Elvis for me.
The TAD, or Tracking Accessory Device.
It can be activated by your compowders.
Infrared heat detector glasses.
The manicure kit with press-on
sticky fingers and laser nail file.
Ooh, does it have
cherry blossom red in it?
- And electric blue.
- Perfect.
(shrieks)
And lastly, the ejector bead bracelet.
Careful with that one.
It's still in development.
By the way,
I like your new look, Clover.
Very sophisticated.
- My mother has a suit just like it.
- (girls snigger)
GIRLS: Huh?
(all scream)
ALL: Cool!
Look at all the toys. How...
- Awesome.
- Cool.
..childish.
WOMAN: Did you see how wonderful
the Vladimir Kozyrev Line was?
WOMAN 2: You have to see
that Vladimir line.
MAN: Vladimir Kozyrev is
the most popular at the convention.
Guess we know where to start.
ALL: Cool!
I'd say we're definitely
in the right place.
Welcome to the Vladimir Kozyrev Booth.
Thanks. We hear your toys
are all the rage.
What my associate means
to articulate is,
is that we've, uh, observed
a positive reaction to your toy line.
Yeah, they're all the rage.
I've never heard of
Vladimir Kozyrev before.
- Are his toys in stores yet?
- No. We're a brand-new company.
Really? No one's had a chance
to play with them?
REP: This is our big debut.
I see.
Why don't you take some toys?
- Hey!
- Go on. Open them.
You'll see their appeal instantly.
Really.
Maybe later. Right now
we need to make a phone call.
JERRY:Hello, ladies.
How's the toy fair?
We're sending samples your way
from the Vladimir Kozyrev Toy Company.
Ow!
The rep said the company's brand new,
but the packaging's ancient.
Like from the Seventies.
Not only that, all the toys in the WOOHP
playback were from their toy line.
Good work, girls.
I'll let you know what we find out.
Let's go over the mission
while we wait to hear from Jerry.
Better yet, let's go over
how I'm going to impress Rick
while we're stuck in stupid Taiwan.
Taiwan's not stupid, Clover.
It's exotic and interesting.
Good angle. Why didn't I think of that?
(compowder ringing)
Hi, Rick. It's Clover.
Oh, nothing much. I'm just calling
from exotic and interesting Taiwan.
- (beeping)
- That was fast.
Huh? Jerry says there's no record of
a Vladimir Kozyrev company anywhere.
Well, somebody has to be
making these toys.
Sam? Are you OK?
- (chuckles)
- (gasps)
(laughs)
Rick, I'm gonna have to call you back.
- This is so sixth grade.
- Yeah, Sammy. Cut it out.
- Make me.
- (growls)
Leave me alone! No!
Do something, Clover.
Make her stop acting like a kid.
- What do I look like, her mother?
- Well, in that outfit...
(grunts in frustration)
You behave,
or you're going to your room.
- Huh?
- (sighs)
ALEX:
We better tell Jerry what's going on.
- Hi, Jerry.
-Look, everyone. It's Clover.
Red Rover, Red Rover, send Clover over.
(all laugh)
(both shriek)
Oh, no. Not Jerry too!
We have to figure out
what's up with these toys
before Jerry and Sam and everyone
are stuck like this forever.
(whispers) It's just the same old stuff
we saw when we were here before.
The Barkaroo!
Shh!
Ooh, Megatronic-action hero!
- The Beauty Queen! Yeah!
- Shh!
(gasps)
It's Mommy's doll.
They have Mommy's doll!
Hey, my mom had one of those, too.
The Little Ann.
She said it was the hottest thing
when she was a kid.
Why? It doesn't even light up.
Let's see who manufactured this baby.
The Little Ann...
- (girls gasp)
- MAN: Hey!
Run!
Trespassers are headed for the alley.
Get rid of them. Permanently.
I don't think
that's a welcoming committee.
(horns blaring)
(sirens blaring)
Jerry was right!
Chaos is turning into pandemonium!
Time for a manicure.
Do you really think there's time?
Cos that electric blue is awesome.
- Press-on sticky fingers.
- Right.
SAM: Whee!
(compowder ringing)
That must be the info
on the Little Ann doll.
Says it was manufactured by The Little
Ann Toy Company in Russia in '74.
They stopped production
a few years later.
Didn't you say the packaging
on the Vladimir Kozyrev line
was from the Seventies?
See who owned
the Little Ann Toy Company.
Vladimir Kozyrev?!
Of course, they're one and the same.
He's still using his old factory
to make these new toys.
Guess we know where we're headed.
(dog barking)
A lot of security for a toy factory.
We need to get inside.
- Oh, look! I want one.
- Shh!
BOTH: Yeah!
- What's that?
- (both scream)
Sam, stop! Sam!
Simon didn't say!
Simon says stop, Sam.
- (alarm wails)
- Intruder alert!
Who put these here?
They're for the next shipment.
Rodney, help me get these inside.
- There's a malfunction in this doll.
- Trash it.
MAN: Grab another two
for the next shipment.
(screams)
BOTH: Yeah!
CLOVER: The TAD says Sam's in here.
This is almost as big as your closet.
Sam, quick! Get out of there!
Simon says, "Get out of there now, Sam!"
(laughs)
That was fun. What else can we play?
(Alex and Clover sigh)
I wonder why they don't close the boxes.
I'll go ask.
I have a better idea.
Let's play I Spy.
- Like we don't do that every day.
- Yeah!
Me first, me first!
I spy with my little eye
something that is...
..big.
- A computer.
- You're good.
I bet that beam has something to do
with everyone acting like kids.
We just have to figure out what
the computer chip is and reprogram it.
I can't log on.
Password's usually obvious cos they
think no one will go for the obvious.
Like... toys.
Huh? OK, Little Ann?
Obviously he doesn't know the rules.
Now what?
BOTH: Huh?
Works for me.
At least it'll slow 'em down
while we...
- MAN: Intruders!
- (girls shriek)
Take that!
Run!
Last one out is a rotten egg!
(all gasp)
How lovely.
- What are you thinking?
- Revenge, of course.
Children who once adored my Little Ann
have grown up and forgotten the joy.
The simplicity.
They're only interested in high-tech
gizmos and silly electronic toys.
Uh, dude, I think
she was talking about the outfit.
Totally.
Now, about this whole "revenge thing."
- It won't bring back the Little Ann.
- Of course it will.
Adults across the world will be forced
to remember the joy of the Little Ann
as soon as I regress them
to the children they once were.
Oh, please, oh, please,
can I go with you?
Please?!
Now, why can't you have
an attitude like that?
Hop aboard, my little elf.
No, Sam! Simon says, "No."
You'll never get away with this!
On second thought, maybe he will.
Once those beams hit us,
we're doomed to a life of immaturity.
Rick will never know the joy of me!
- Hey, it's not my fault.
- Push me!
Where'd they go?
(screams)
(laughs)
Hey, little boy. I'll give you
a lollipop if you untie me.
Oh, OK.
- No sign of Vladimir's sleigh.
- The TAD!
Sam's just ahead of us.
- (both gasp)
- He threw her overboard!
We gotta catch her!
Hang on for hyper-speed.
(girls scream)
He tricked us. It's just a doll.
- Look!
- (screaming)
ALEX: Kozyrev's dolls aren't
turning people into kids anymore.
Now he's using them as an evil army.
We're too late.
Maybe not. What does Vladimir care
about most in the world?
- Bellbottoms?
- The Little Ann.
His pride and joy.
We've gotta beat him at his own game.
Oh!
- I don't get it.
- The old switcheroo.
Don't you mean Barkaroo?
Try to stay with me.
We put the computer chip from
the Barkaroo into the Little Ann.
It's so obvious
he'll never suspect a thing.
Yeah!
I'm on!
- Ow!
- (gasps)
Hey, don't be mean!
- My Little Ann!
- This is the last one, Vladi.
If you throw me over, she goes, too.
(grunts)
My Little Ann.
What do you want to do today,
Little Ann?
Vladimir, you have to go back to
the factory and make things right.
I don't want to. I want to play.
You do it right now, mister,
or you're grounded.
♪ Vladimir's in trouble ♪
Alright.
(bell rings)
- SAM: No way.
- ALEX: Way.
Clover, did I really act like a kid?
Only slightly more than usual.
Hi, Rick.
I have two tickets to the opera.
- Would you care to join me?
- Opera?
Clover, what happened?
You look like my mom now.
Hey, Rick. Are we still going
to the street fair tonight?
Sure, Mandy.
Nice outfit. PTA meeting?
(cackles)
(growls)
Excuse me, professor? Could you tell me
where the administration office is?
(growls)
(screams)
Being mature is so over-rated.