♪ Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop ♪
♪ And then we'll shop ♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby
Here we go, go, go ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ On a mission undercover
and we're in control ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
(screams)
I'm gonna get this role.
Gonna get this role.
You really shouldn't put
so much pressure on yourself.
I'm not. I'm psyching myself up.
And I'm just looking out
for my best friend.
Yeah. Practically everybody in
the school is auditioning.
Everybody who's anybody.
Plus a few nobodies.
(growls)
What are you trying to say, Sam?
I'm not good enough to play
the orphan Cosette?
Of course you are. In fact,
you're the most dramatic person I know.
- But you learning all those lines?
- What?
Starring in a play is about
more than just memorizing lines, Sam.
I wouldn't expect a bookworm like you
to understand art.
That's for true virtuosos,
like Picasso, Da Vinci, Madonna.
And, of course, me.
(both laugh)
Next! Please.
Oh, Monsieur Valjean.
What ill fortune
to be poor with no family.
Uh, I even had to, uh, sell my car
just to be able to get enough to eat.
Thank you. That'll be all, Clover.
- (both applaud)
- Thank you. Thank you, one and all.
I'm so happy to be playing the role
that I so richly deserve.
I'll be signing autographs
in the lunch room.
Uh, Clover, although that was an
interesting interpretation ofLes Mis,
it's not exactly
what we're looking for.
- Next!
- (shrieks)
(sobs)
Clover, aren't you getting
a little carried away?
- It's just a silly play.
- A silly play?
This is my career we're talking about.
I mean, how could he not pick me?
I have perfect hair, perfect teeth.
Plus, I just love Paris.
I'd like to see Mr Tetley's
teaching credentials.
You know, you should be happy
you didn't get this part.
I mean, rehearsing over and over.
"Oh, Monsieur Valjean, what ill fortune
to be poor with no family."
- Sounds like such a drag.
- That's it!
That was brilliant, Samantha.
You were born to play Cosette.
And I won't take no for an answer.
Uh, thanks a lot, Mr Tetley,
but Clover should really get this part.
You know, she's a very talented actress.
Plus, she has great teeth.
- See?
- But you've got the makings of a star!
No, really, Clover's my girlfriend
and I...
- Perhaps even a Hollywood star.
- When do rehearsals start?
"When do rehearsals start?"
I can't believe you, you little traitor!
It's not my fault I'm star material.
Cut it out, you guys.
You're supposed to be friends.
Since you girls are
in such a talkative mood,
perhaps you would like to tell us
what you think the most dramatic scene
inLes Misérablesis.
Well, I for one think it's the scene
in which Jean Valjean
escapes through the Paris sewers.
- Greetings, my academic colleagues.
- Ah, you must be Percival.
- The Trobokistan ambassador's son.
- Indubitably.
Oh, by the way, sir,
I always felt it would be appropriate
to discussLes Misérables
in the context of a major strain
in 19th-century literature
emphasizing pauperization.
Hmm, an interesting theory, Percival.
You should do just fine
in tomorrow's quiz.
Quiz? What quiz?
The quiz on
the first ten chapters ofLes Mis.
That is, for those of you
who didn't get a role in the play.
(growls)
So, do you girls want to go
to the mall tonight?
I would, but now I have a quiz
to study for.
You know, ever since
somebody stole my part in the play.
- How about you, Sam?
- I have to go over my lines.
You know what they say.
The more practice, the more perfect.
(sighs) I guess I'll go it alone then.
(all scream)
Nice timing, Jerry.
Yeah, we were in the middle
of an important fight.
Sorry, girls.
But it's an international emergency.
You see, the annual Nobel Prize winners'
conference is going on today.
The world's top scholars are there.
International emergency?
Sounds more like
an international snooze-fest.
Yeah, where can we not get tickets?
JERRY: As you can see on
this hotel surveillance video,
several prize winners have been
mysteriously kidnapped.
- They must be found.
- (groans)
Did I mention
the conference is in Paris?
ALL: Paris?!
And now for the gadgets.
This week we have
steel cable launcher go-go boots,
jet pack backpacks,
infra-red heat-detector glasses,
exploding lipstick and, last but not
least, emergency propeller watches,
vibrant spring colors.
One more thing, tomorrow you'll be
having a surprise quiz in biology.
Two quizzes in one day?
That's totally unfair.
Unfair for some of us.
Couldn't you at least tell us
what the quiz is on, Jer?
Sorry, but it would be
completely unethical for me
to disclose that the test is
covering the chapter on Cro-Magnon Man.
- Oops.
- ALL: Huh?
Oh, would you look at the time?
I've really got to run.Ciao.
I hope this thing's on autopilot.
(chatter)
- WOMAN: Vacuumed up?
- WOMAN 2: Vanished?!
MAN: But why?
OK, spies. Keep your eyes open for
anything strange and try to blend in.
Excuse me, miss.
Aren't you the one who wrote the article
about the expansion of the universe?
That's me. Brains and beauty.
And yourself? What have you written?
Well, my specialty is prehistoric man.
- In particular, Cro-Magnon.
- Can you believe it?
This guy could actually help us
on our biology quiz.
Friends and colleagues, the specialist
on the expansion of the universe
has honored us with her presence.
Would you be so kind as
to share your latest findings with us?
(chuckles nervously)
OK, um, actually,
the universe is as easy as pie.
It's like... one big shopping mall.
Yeah! That's it.
See, it starts out small,
but the more business it does,
the more it expands.
So, no need to worry.
By the way, did I tell you
I just love Paris?
(screaming)
- I don't see anything.
- SAM: Me neither.
It's like she vanished into thin air.
(screaming)
What a disaster.
He's the foremost authority
on 19th-century French literature.
SAM: OK, this is officially weird.
Weird would be an understatement, Sammy.
Two people just got vacuumed
into the ceiling like dust bunnies.
No, not the abductions,
the people who got abducted.
Um, you wanna try that again in English,
Miss Cosette?
Think about it.
Jerry tells us we'll be quizzed
on Cro-Magnon Man in biology tomorrow
and the Cro-Magnon specialist
gets kidnapped.
We're also supposed to have a test
onLes Misérables,and guess what?
The expert on 19th-century
French literature vanished.
First of all, "we" aren't being
tested onLes Misérables.
Second of all,
do you expect us to believe
that there's a connection between these
kidnappings and our quizzes in LA?
That's exactly what I expect
you to believe, Miss Sore Loser.
ALEX: Easy does it, girls.
Look, we'll just ask Jerry for
the subject of all our upcoming quizzes,
and then see if any of the prize winners
are experts on those subjects.
No way. Absolutely not.
I am not allowed
to reveal quiz subjects to you girls.
But this is different.
It's for our mission.
It could be a matter of life and... and
someone being sucked into the ceiling.
(sighs)
Well, when you put it that way...
Your next quiz is in math class.
The topic is Isaac Newton.
But that's all I'm telling you.
Since when do we study
cookie designers in math class?
Newton isn't a cookie designer,
you dimwit.
- Who you calling a dimwit, traitor?
- (bell dings)
Hey, girls. There's an expert on Isaac
Newton here in the conference catalogue.
ALEX: He went into that restaurant.
Are you two still harping on
that role in the play?
You obviously have never been stabbed
in the back by one of your best friends.
Ah-ha! I knew it. You admit
that Sam's one of your best friends.
ALEX: Hey, look at this.
(screams)
We gotta get down there.
Our expert's clearly the next in line.
You're in danger!
(screams)
Quick. The jet pack backpacks.
Help!
Incredible. The kidnappers vacuum
their victims up into these tubes.
Not if we have anything to say about it.
Let our friend go, right now!
And tell us why you've kidnapped
the Nobel Prize winners.
(evil laughter)
Oh, well, look at the time. Gotta fly.
(chuckles nervously)
I think you mean, "Gotta run."
Hey, don't leave me here!
I thought we were friends!
(screams)
- CLOVER: What now, Miss Bookworm?
- How should I know?
Well, you better think
of something fast, Cosette.
Wait, that's it. InLes Misérables,
Jean Valjean escapes through the sewers.
Look out!
Ew, nast! I'd rather fight those jerks
than go into this filthy pipe.
I mean, hello! My complexion is
too sensitive...
(squeals)
Oh, you'll pay for this, Sam.
And I mean that literally.
It's gonna cost a fortune
to have my go-go boots cleaned.
MAN: Forget about them.
We'll just interrogate their girlfriend.
Good luck trying to pry
anything out of that one.
Oh, I can be very persuasive.
You're lucky Sam thought of the sewers.
Otherwise,
you would've been French toast.
Wait a second. I'm getting
a weak signal from Alex's compowder.
I'll patch it through.
Help! What are you two waiting for,
an invitation?
I'm locking in on her location.
Oh, my. It appears she's being held
at 12118 Marmalade Street.
- But that's...
- The house next door to mine.
That's right.
And according to WOOHP records,
that's where the ambassador from
Trobokistan and his son
have been living.
Isn't that the fat-headed kid
from Mr Tetley's class?
Yeah. We'd better get back
to Beverly Hills.
CLOVER: Farewell, gay Paris.
MAN: I'm gonna ask you one last time.
Where's WOOHP headquarters?
I wouldn't tell you in a million years,
chump.
Just you wait and see what I do to you
when I get out of here.
OK, you wanna play games? Fine.
I got a game for you.
(screams)
(drilling)
It's about time you two got here!
- I warned you not to mess with me.
- (growls)
(screams)
Not bad for a bookworm.
- Now let's find the prize winners.
- (door opening)
We've got all three of them, boss.
Good. Bring 'em in.
Hey, it's the big-head freak
from our school.
Pi R-squared times
logarithm of ZY equals...
It's like they're sucking
the intelligence from the prize winners
and putting it into his head.
No wonder he's such a know-it-all.
ALL: Mr Ambassador.
ALL: Ambassador?
That's right, girls.
And also soon the father of
the most intelligent child in the world.
My son will be a genius in no time.
A star pupil in school.
No one will dare pick on him
the way they picked on me.
So, let me get this straight.
You kidnapped scholars
to suck out their brains
and pump them into your son's head?
- Yes.
- And you think he won't get picked on?
Hello, the guy's head is
the size of a hot-air balloon.
(girls laugh)
We'll see who gets the last laugh.
- He's gonna turn us into hamsters!
- Keen observation.
The hamster is really going to benefit
from your intelligence.
(girls scream)
- Hey, Alex, do that again.
- No way! It hurts!
If you keep it up,
you might break through.
(alarm blares)
That was close.
- Another job well done, girls.
- ALL: Thanks, Jerry.
Wait a minute. Couldn't you have
broken out of your cylinders yourselves?
- You both have propeller watches.
- Um, yeah, I suppose.
(scoffs) Yeah, and risk getting
unsightly facial bruises?
I don't think so.
Um, girls? Aren't you forgetting
something important?
(screams)
(strains)
That is one freak show
I want no part of.
Hey, what do you know? It's working!
Nice job, Alex. You saved the world.
Guess this means from now on he'll have
to study for tests like the rest of us.
Oh, wait. I forgot.
Some of us are exempt from tests.
(squeals)
Lucky thing there was almost
no fluid left in the tube.
You alright, girls?
A little grossed out,
but otherwise fine.
I can't... I can't believe
you just did that for me.
You totally saved my life, Sam.
Not to mention my outfit.
Well, I wouldn't have done it
for just anybody.
- Only for a best friend?
- Exactly.
Oh, Sammy! I'm so sorry
I called you a thief and a traitor!
No, I should be sorry. I never should
have accepted the role of Cosette.
(gasps) Oh, no! It's time for
our quiz onLes Misérables!
No!
CLOVER: Quick, to Beverly High!
I forgot all about it! Heck, I don't
know squat aboutLes Misérables.
Neither do I.
BOTH: What are we gonna do?!
Don't worry about it, girls. I'll tell
you everything you need to know.
After all,
that's what best friends are for.
Good. Cos we also need help cramming
for our biology quiz on the Cro-Mags.
Hmm...
Wow. Who knew an artist like me
could also excel at academics?
Looks like we're all multi-talented.
Speaking of which, what did you guys
decide to do about the play?
It's simple.
I'm going to convince Mr Tetley
that Clover is the right actress
for the part of Cosette.
And I'm going to insist that
he make Sam my first understudy.
Mr Tetley,
we need to talk to you right away.
- Yeah, it's about the part of Cosette.
- Shh. Not now, girls.
MANDY: Oh, Monsieur Valjean.
What ill fortune to be poor
with no family.
That's it! That was brilliant, Mandy.
You were born to play Cosette,
and I won't take no for an answer.
BOTH: Huh?
Mandy, you've got
the makings of a star!
Tell me something I don't know.
That thief!
- CLOVER: That traitor!
- SAM: That back-stabber!
Here we go again.