♪ Here we go,
we're getting on the road till we stop ♪
♪ And then we'll shop ♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ On a mission undercover
and we're in control ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
This is Professor John Payley.
Diary entry: Thursday, 08.00 hours.
I'm baffled.
Every vulcanologist
considers this a dormant volcano.
But if that's true, then why...?
(gasps) What on earth...?!
What on earth...?!
(school bell)
(screaming)
(all grunt)
Oh, that was, like, the perfect end
to our harshest mission yet.
For sure! After what we've been through,
school will be a breeze.
ALEX: Good thing tomorrow night
is the big dance!
I so need to unwind!
MANDY: Don't kick back yet, girls.
This afternoon is the track meet
and having you three on our team...
..makes me glad I'm not.
(gasps) The track meet! We forgot!
(screams)
(yells)
(gasps)
(Alex screams)
ALEX: Oh, I hope I can move by tomorrow,
and I hope the dance will help us
forget the way we blew the track meet!
Oh, don't say "dance" Alex.
It makes my feet hurt more.
- SAM: Let's just relax.
- CLOVER: Yeah...relax...
(sighs)
(all scream)
(surprised grunts)
Well, so glad you could drop in, ladies.
Like we had a choice?
Jerry, tell me you're kidding.
I mean, we just got back from
the most intense mission we ever had.
We are wiped! Trashed! Tweaked!
Relax.
ALEX: How, when you're about
to send us on another mission?
A mission to relax.
You're no asset to WOOHP
when you're stressed,
so I'm sending you on vacation, here.
- GIRLS: Oh!
- Let me guess.
This is a bullet-proof covering we use
for escaping from a jungle prison?
No, this is a towel you use
for drying off after a swim.
Ah-ha, I bet this is a high-speed drill
and a tube of blasting gel
to blow out a wall!
No, a beach umbrella and sunscreen
to stop a sunburn.
And before you ask,
that's a nose clip for swimming.
Oh, that's the Gadget Emergency Kit.
A precaution. You won't need it.
Let me get this straight...
You're sending us somewhere to have fun?
JERRY: How does Hawaii sound?
Too good to be true.
I have just one question...
When does our flight leave?
In one minute. Just step in here.
This elevator's kinda small.
Does it take us right to our plane?
Oh, there's no plane.
A cruise missile is much faster.
Bon voyage, ladies!
Huh?
GIRLS: Jerry! I never fly by missile!
I'm totally claustrophobed!
(all scream)
(all yell)
(all grunt)
Hi! I'm Julie, your WOOHP travel agent!
You must be Sam, Clover and Alex.
I have your vacation all set!
Julie, could you be not quite so perky?
Huh?
I can't believe it,
we're really in Hawaii!
This is like my ultimate fantasy trip!
Up the beach, we have hula dancing!
If it'll get you to dial down
the perkiness, I'm there.
My kind of dance is the Taualunga.
Or you could just lie back
and work on your tan!
Now that's my kind of work.
(sighs)
I want action!
Like tomorrow night when we rock out
to the finest band in Beverly Hills...
Ultra Loud Zone!
(shrieks)
Whoops! My board got away from me.
My name's Alex. Who are you?
Corey, I came here to study volcanoes
with my college professor,
which is totally cool cos Hawaii
is my ultimate fantasy trip.
Really? Mine, too!
Excellent!
Yeah, I love the food,
the people, the music...
- Though I'm not much at hula dancing.
- No?
Well, my favorite dance is one
you might never have heard of.
It's called the Taualunga.
Mine too! This is almost, like, destiny!
- Who's your favorite band?
- Oh, wow, that's tough.
There's thousands to choose from but
I'd have to say my favorite is Ultra...
BOTH: Loud Zone!
(thump)
Are you doing anything later?
No, Professor Payley
was supposed to bring me
to his camp at that dormant volcano,
but he never showed.
Hey, wanna catch a wave?
Oh, sure!
Hey, surfin' is the only life for me.
(gasps)
Right. I just gotta go
tell my friend where I'll be.
Clover, have you got a minute?
I need you to tell me how to surf.
Huh?
Corey, how big do these waves get?
Oh, three. Maybe four.
- Feet?
- Stories.
Four stories?!
Here we go!
(Alex screams)
Awesome! C'mon, Alex!
Corey, I have a confession!
I never surfed anything bigger
than, uh, a 35-foot wave!
OK, hold on, Alex!
Corey!
ALEX: Sam! Clover! Help!
Clover, give me a hand!
Get me out of here!
We're coming, Alex!
Get in!
(all scream)
- Anyone injured?
- I have critical split-end damage.
And Corey's gone!
He stood right there and
vanished in a burst of fire.
It was like a volcano erupting!
This doesn't look like sand to me.
- It's obsidian, volcanic glass!
- Is there anything you don't know?
Corey said his professor flaked out
and never showed for his field trip
to study that volcano!
There's a connection
between the missing volcano prof
and Corey going up in smoke?
I got a bad feeling about this.
I'm calling Jerry.
Jerry, this Sam. Hello? Hello?
Hello, Sam. Are you there?
I don't read you, sorry.
Forget it, your com-powder got wet.
We'll try ours.
Maybe there's something
in the kit we can use.
"Computer Spy Manual."
ALEX: Type in "volcano."
Let's see what comes up.
WOOHP has a Volcano
Research Lab in Iceland.
Maybe they can answer our questions.
Iceland? Where it's like, all icy?
So? Corey needs our help!
Alex is right, Clover.
We have a duty to check this out.
Hi!
Julie, we have to get to Iceland.
Oh, no problem! I'll arrange it!
I swear, if she doesn't stop grinning...
(girls gasp)
Not again!
ALEX: Can somebody
please scratch my neck?
CLOVER: Ow! Get your toe out of my eye!
(all scream)
(groans) This is so cold!
What are you doing in Iceland
dressed like this?
C-could we d-discuss this over
a hot, grande, d-decaf soy latte?
SAM: Dr Sorenson, we need to know
if you've had any reports
of volcanic eruptions in Hawaii.
SORENSON: We had one yesterday
and one earlier today.
Both were near a dormant volcano,
so we assumed they were false alarms.
If there were eruptions,
we'd have heard from our vulcanologist,
Professor Payley.
GIRLS: Professor Payley?
He's been missing since yesterday,
and his mega-cute student Corey
vanished earlier today!
(alarm)
Now I know we have a bug in the system.
(beeping)
You sure the eruptions aren't real?
My dear, if all these volcanoes
were to erupt at once,
it would mean massive
global destruction.
So, it's safe to go back to Hawaii?
Well, if people are disappearing there,
I wouldn't call it safe.
You're not thinking of going back?
(groans)
How did they get these things
in the kit?
Pass me the binocular shades.
I don't see any sign of Payley.
Can we just go home now?
Wait a sec, I see something down there.
SAM: Looks like glass!
Whoa!
Watch your step.
(sighs) Clover, I owe you big-time.
You guys OK down there?
(gasps)
Whoa! Didn't think you'd
pay me back so soon.
Forget the he-went-home theory.
He wouldn't leave these.
Look, a camcorder!
Hey, let's make a video of us!
Don't! It may have recorded a clue!
Let's rewind and see what he was doing.
What on earth...?!
There was an eruption!
And Prof. Payley vanished
just like Corey!
One problem, Alex.
If this was all molten lava yesterday,
how come the rocks look
totally the same today?
Let me see. Alex, walk out there.
Is this where he was standing?
Exactly. See this crack?
Duh! It's so obvious this is a trap...
(all scream)
(groans)
Corey! You're all right!
Alex, get out of here before
they catch you like they did us!
HENCHMAN: Intruders!
ALEX: I'll be back for you, Corey!
(girls gasp)
We just hit Volcano Central!
ALEX: It looks like that humongous laser
keeps the lava cooking!
I bet this place is wired into
every other volcano on earth!
What kind of freak came up with this?
That would be me!
(all gasp)
Dr Hefestus is the name,
global devastation is my game.
Forgive me if I startled you.
Meeting people is so awkward.
Let's try this again, from the TOP!
Stop them!
Ow, my foot!
Don't mess...with our...vacation!
Put that down before someone gets hurt.
Like you!
(grunts)
HEFESTUS: Uh-uh-uh! Careful, girls.
Volcanic fire ruined my face.
As it will... yours.
My machine can erupt
every volcano on earth!
(beeping)
And when the world is covered in lava,
you all will look like me!
(evil laughter)
You have serious issues, though I'm sure
it's nothing a facial wouldn't cure.
I can relate. That week I had a pimple,
I was a major witch.
True, but we still loved you anyway.
Your evil plan won't succeed, Hefestus.
Not if we have anything to say about it!
(evil laughter)
ALEX: I guess we don't have
anything to say about it.
We're almost in the lava
and this heat is trashing my hair!
Heat? Maybe my com-powder is dry!
Jerry! Jerry?
Ah, forget it.
Sam calling Dr Sorenson!
Sam! Are you all right?
Well, we're kinda hung up, DrS.
Can you reach Jerry?
I'm a little busy myself!
Every volcano on earth
is starting to blow!
ALEX: We have to do something!
Molten lava's about to cover the world!
Not to mention our hair!
Alex, give me your nose-clip!
You go, cowgirl!
(whirring)
Seize them!
I knew he'd say that. Split up!
(shrieks)
(gasps)
(shocked cries)
(yells)
Now, tell me where the keys are
so I can let my friends out!
I got your keys right here.
Hey!
Help us trash that volcano machine!
- We have to turn this off now!
- Yeah.
(crackling)
The lava's almost to our level!
Hot-foot alert!
Hey! (sniffs)
- I smell garlic.
- Huh?
This is hot, as in spicy.
It's definitely not lava.
- It's marinara sauce!
- HEFESTUS: That's right, ladies.
CLOVER: Hefestus!
There is no Hefestus.
GIRLS: Jerry?!
SAM: And your henchmen
are really WOOHP agents?
And Corey is really...?
Goofy!
You're not trying to destroy the world?
What's going on?
It was all part of the test.
- Everything was fake?
- Yes.
This phony volcano was once
an arch-villain's hideout.
Now I use it for our annual field test.
- You were testing us?
- Did we pass?
Uh, no.
The lava got you
before you could save the world.
So, you all have to undergo re-training.
Corey, you were in on this?
M-my name's Morey, n-not Corey.
So your favorite dance
isn't the Taualunga?
Sorry. Your beach bag was bugged.
I don't even dance.
(rumbling)
What is this, Jerry, extra credit?
No! This is real!
Great. We blow the track meet,
I fall for a dork, and now this!
There is an actual volcano under
your fake one and it's erupting!
(screams)
(shrieks)
They'll never be able to move all
that stone in time! We're trapped!
Get back! That's real lava!
This is too ironic!
Look out!
If only we could fly through there!
That's it! Alex, your parachute's
back in the Emergency Kit, right?
Yeah, but what can we do with it?
Make a hot-air balloon, if we can
stretch the chute across the crack.
Leave it to me!
Everybody, hold on tight!
(explosion)
We made it, thanks to you girls.
You showed real resourcefulness!
You still going to flunk us?
JERRY: No, you pass, with flying colors!
CLOVER: Cool!
Now, how about a real vacation?
I've heard of guys being two-faced,
but Morey was ridiculous.
Let's forget Hawaii
and just enjoy the dance.
I wonder what theme they picked.
(cheering)
(Hawaiian-style music)
GIRLS: No! Not that! Anything but this!
They seriously need to get a life.
(cheering continues)