♪Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop♪
♪And then we'll shop♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪On a mission undercover
and we're in control♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show♪
♪Here we go, here we go♪
♪Here we go♪
MAN: Get him!
MAN: Give it up.
Prepare to meet your demise.
Give up!
(screams)
(cheering)
(shrieking)
Look at that.
We made it to school in record time.
Think of how much more time
we could have saved
if those pedestrians would have just
stayed off the sidewalks.
Cool motorcycle.
Who's the intense biker babe?
That must be Donna Ramone. I heard
she was just released from juvie.
Looks more like
she escaped from juvie.
Come on, guys.
I'm sure she's perfectly nice.
Hi, I'm Alex.
I don't think we've met.
- Oops!
- (growls)
You know what happened
to the last person who touched my ride?
Let's just say she eats her dinner
through a straw these days!
(laughs awkwardly) What a coincidence.
I like protein shakes, too.
(school bell rings)
Oh, gee. There goes the bell.
See you around.
(Donna shrieks)
Oops. Sorry.
(whistle sounds)
Maybe I'll just use the entrance
at the other end of the school.
(grunts) What a stressful day.
I hope I never see that thug again.
At least they're serving my favorite
lunch today, soy cheese pizza.
- I'll take that.
- Hey, give me my pizza back!
Not a chance.
Way I figure, you owe me lunch money
for a year after what happened today.
Alex, you're not going to let her
extort you like that.
Yeah, stand up for yourself!
I... I'm not gonna pay.
In fact... I want my pizza back!
On second thought,
you can keep it.
I'm gonna turn you
into my own personal hand puppet!
- (shrieks)
- GIRL: Teacher!
You're lucky... for now.
But tomorrow at three o'clock,
you're dead meat.
ALEX: You hear that? I'm dead meat.
Don't sweat it, Alex.
I'm sure this'll all blow over.
When it does, give me a call.
Until then, I'll be at the North Pole.
(all scream)
Can I offer you girls a sandwich?
- No, thanks. We just ate.
- Some of us did.
Have you ever heard
of a television show calledFight?
That wrestling show
that takes place on the island?
That's the one.Fight.Fear Island
Gladiator Habi-Tat.Fight.
I love that show. What's up?
Well, it seems that what's up is
one of the contestants,
an Olympic decathlete
named Reggie Willis,
hasn't been heard from
since losing on the show.
I wouldn't mind getting lost with him.
He's hot.
Yes, well, in addition to being hot,
he's supposed to represent the United
States in the Olympics next month.
Which brings us to your mission.
I want you girls to go undercover
onFight
to find out what happened to him.
- Undercover in what capacity?
- As contestants, of course.
I was afraid he'd say that.
And now for your gadgets.
Zip-line bracelets, parachute belts,
mini-ski aerobic sneakers,
laser heat hairdryers,
buzzsaw wristwatches
and lip balm smoke bombs.
Ooh! I could use a little lip relief.
(all shriek)
Enjoy the mission, girls.
This is Fear Island?
I don't see anything scary about it.
(horn honking)
I stand corrected.
Vince King's the name,
promoting human combat is my game!
You must be our new contestants!
That's right.
I'm Sam, and this is Clover and Alex.
Terrific.
Let me give you the grand tour.
KING:Fightis
an international sensation.
It's seen in every nation
of the world.
Every terrain of the world is
represented on my island.
Fighthas
the most fantastic playing field
in any sport ever conceived!
This is remarkable.
Arnold, has Donna cooled down yet?
Did she call off the fight?
Are you kidding?
Things are just starting to heat up.
Smart money's on Donna,
but you're an attractive long shot.
Ooh!
So, Mr King, have you heard about
the disappearance of Reggie Willis?
Probably afraid to show his face
in public
after his brutal defeat
at the hands of my merciless gladiators.
Brutal? Merciless? Are you saying
that the fighting on your show is real?
Oh, of course not. It's just... showbiz.
All of our action is choreographed
and safety is a premium.
(girls coughing)
Hit the dressing room, ladies.
Suit up and meet me on stage.
The show starts in an hour!
And I thought Sam's driving was bad.
(coughs)
ALEX: What is this, a wedgie suit?
(cheering)
Tell me about it. No wonder
everyone on this island wants to fight.
Now, let's meet the contestants!
(crowd cheers)
The lovely Sam, Alex, and Clover
will risk
life and limb to try and win this.
The covetedFightbelt!
(whoops)
But first they have to make it past
my highly trained, hand-picked
international gladiators!
Are you ready?
(crowd cheers)
On your mark, girls. Get set...
Release the wolves!
!ALL: Wolves?
Pick up the pace, girls!
Those wolves look awfully hungry!
And we look like lunch!
Please!
King said this is all just showbiz.
These pups wouldn't hurt a fly.
Apparently no one told the wolves
it's only showbiz.
- ALEX: Great! What now?
- Climb up!
Is there still time to throw ourselves
to the wolves?
Get off my back!
Yay!
Oh, great. The one day I forget
to use moisture-wear eyeliner.
Over there!
(crowd cheers)
Huh? What do I have to do
to get rid of these guys?
Get your hands off me.
I'm not your prom date!
Uh-oh.
See you next fall.
(gladiators scream)
(crowd cheers)
I hope this outfit isn't dry-clean-only.
Hmm? Hello. What do we have here?
Whoa.
This island has everything
except a mall.
There she is!
- Give it up, sweetheart.
- Not a chance.
Don't these beefcakes ever take a break?
A sewer in an ancient city? Oh, well.
Never look a gift horse in the mouth.
How's the mission going?
Great, if you like running
for your life from homicidal gladiators.
Bad news. It turns out several more
athletes who competed on "Fight"
have seemingly vanished.
That's not hard to imagine.
Gotta go.
What the...?
Seize them!
(gasps)
I'd give my entire shoe collection
for some relief from this heat.
Ouch!
Not exactly what I had in mind.
(crowd cheers)
Yay!
Mind if I borrow this?
(crowd cheers)
Help! I'm drowning!
Why do I have to be such a nice person?
What's this gaudy thing?
This is the farthest anyone's
ever made it!
Who are these girls?
- Sammy!
- Alex, you're alive!
Just barely. The island's crawling
with those muscleheads.
(rustling)
- BOTH: Clover!
- You can get off me anytime now.
I got a hunch that Reggie
never left the island.
Not alive, at least.
The quicker we find out what happened
to Reggie,
the quicker we can get off this island.
Maybe the underground captives can
give us some answers.
I saw them in the sewer when I was
running from the gladiators. Weird, huh?
Come to think of it,
I saw something weird, too.
A satellite was following me
down by the river.
And then suddenly it disappeared.
Does this qualify as weird?
It came off one of the gladiators.
Looks like an electronic collar.
Prisoners, a satellite
and an electronic collar.
King is definitely up to something.
I think it's time to talk
to the prisoners.
They're the only people on this island
who haven't tried to destroy us.
CLOVER: For being
glamorous international spies,
we spend an awful lot of time
creeping through stinky sewers.
ALEX: Wait a second.
These people look familiar.
They're professional athletes. And
probably formerFightcontestants.
And now King is keeping them here
to work on his island.
We've got to save them!
Great! Who's gonna save us?
I've got to hand it to you girls.
You've got the moves.
You've got the skills.
You've made it further
than any other contestant!
But most importantly,
the audience loves you.
Excuse us if we don't seem appreciative
of your compliments.
That's OK.
You can show your appreciation
by working as warriors on my island.
And once I whip you into shape,
I think you'll make fine gladiators.
Uh, as if.
You must be out of your mind
if you think you're gonna turn us
into gladiators.
Oh, I'm not.
But my Temperament Collars will.
ALL: Huh?
I can control the moods of every
gladiator with a remote control.
I can make my gladiators
as docile as kitties
or as vicious as cornered pit-bulls.
And you do it all from the comfort
and safety of your studio.
You never even have
to get your hands dirty.
That's the idea.
Fit them with the collars.
I need to check our ratings.
CLOVER: Reggie!
I don't know how to repay you.
You saved me when you fished me out
of that lake and pulled my collar off.
That was you?
There's no need to repay me.
But I like foreign movies,
white roses and chocolate.
Rude way to show your appreciation, Sam.
It's her collar. It's been activated.
You'll never capture
theFightbelt!
We gladiators will never allow it!
CLOVER: We've got to save Sam.
How can we while she's under
the power of that collar?
She's got that crazy look in her eyes,
like when there's a half-off sale
at the mall.
If we can't take off the collar,
maybe we can block King's signal.
If we could only find the origin...
Wait a second.
Maybe the signal has something
to do with that satellite.
I've seen the satellite, too.
It's worth a shot.
(crowd cheers)
This isn't right!
They're supposed to have collars on!
Let's see how they do
against my gladiators now.
There it is!
How are we going to take out
the satellite
with those super gladiators out there?
If we could just get past them,
maybe we could scale the cliff.
If we only had a decoy.
(sighs) Why am I always the decoy?
Hey, knuckleheads! Here I am!
Think you can catch me?
Stop her!
(crowd cheers)
No one wins on my show!
My gladiators are unbeatable!
I'm unbeatable!
Look out! It's King!
(whoops)
(crowd boos)
Sam? You look tense.
What do you say I take that collar off
and give you a nice relaxing massage?
(screams)
Nice shot. Too bad rock throwing isn't
an Olympic event.
You'd win the gold for sure.
(screams)
Sam, don't do it!
Don't you remember me?
I'm Alex! We're best friends!
We were best friends!
(screams)
You'll never get the belt.
No one beats me!
Reggie...
Hey, King! Your gladiators are
the biggest wimps I've ever fought.
And I'm gonna win that belt.
Reggie, watch out!
No!
ALEX: Help!
Alex? What are you doing?
What am I doing? What are you doing?
Pull me in!
No! My gladiators!
You did it! You won!
No. We won!
CROWD: Reggie! Reggie! Reggie!
(bell rings)
Isn't it great to be off that island
of fighting gladiators
and back in Beverly Hills?
I am so ready to give peace a chance.
You ready to rumble, wimp?
STUDENTS: Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
(growls)
Listen here, you big Neanderthal!
I've been chased by wild wolves,
had boulders thrown at me
and fought gladiators all night.
So if you want a piece of me,
let's get it on!
Hmm.
For a bony runt, you're pretty tough.
I am? I mean... you bet I am!
I didn't know you had it in you.
Guess you're cooler than I thought.
We're gonna have to get you a ride.
We are? Cool!
Well, at least something good
came out of all this.
Yeah? Like what?
Now that Alex is getting a motorcycle,
I won't have to ride to school
with you anymore.
- Ta-da!
- What do you mean? Come back here!