♪ Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop ♪
♪ And then we'll shop ♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ On a mission undercover
and we're in control ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
Hey, Toby, put that fantasy junk away!
Yeah, how about the reality of
getting the chores done before sunup?
But this is the best part.
The aliens are about to land!
Oh, my!
ALL: Whoa!
DRIVING INSTRUCTOR:
Left! Straighten out! Right! Look out!
I seriously suggest you get yourself
a bus schedule, young lady,
because at this rate, there's no way
you'll pass your driving test!
ALEX: But I've got to pass!
Girls who drive attract three times more
boys than girls who don't!
Don't worry, Alex! We know
you'll come through in the clutch!
Please... don't say "clutch!"
ALL: Huh?
(they scream)
You're the one taking driver's ed, Alex!
Where are the brakes!?
Is this WOOHP? I can't see anything.
I should've bought that glow-in-the-dark
tank top at the mall.
Have I mentioned I don't like the dark?
I'm not scared. You never know what's...
- (they scream)
- Hello, girls.
Jerry!
You know what stress does to my skin!
Sorry. Agent Morrison tripped over
the generator cable again.
Now, take a look at these satellite
tapes from Italy, Russia and France.
WOOHP has reason to believe the people
in these videos were abducted by aliens.
(they laugh)
Aliens? You're kidding, right?
Did you bonk your head
in the shower this morning?
This is serious, spies. These abductions
occurred in the last two weeks.
The first one was in
this Iowa cornfield.
Your mission is to visit
the abduction site and look for clues.
I knew we couldn't be alone
in the galaxy!
I knew there was life on other planets!
Hey, Alex, you sound like
you're from another planet!
Yeah, Planet What-ever!
Your equipment will include
some old favorites:
Jet-Pack Backpacks;
Hair-Pick Lock Picks;
Heat Sensor 6000
Infrared Motion-Detector Sunglasses,
now with wireless internet connections
and digital camera functions.
Some new items:
Wrist-Mounted Grapplo-XGs; and CLALG.
Ew. Need a glass of water, Jerry?
That's "CLALG." C-L-A-L-G.
Combination Laser And Lip Gloss.
In fruity low-cal bubble gum flavor.
If there are aliens out there, we'll
show them the best Earth has to offer.
BOTH: Yay, Earth!
Goodbye, and good luck, ladies.
(they scream)
PILOT: This is your WOOHP pilot. We're
flying over the Midwest at 37,000 feet.
If you'll look out the bottom
of the plane, you'll see Iowa.
Bottom of the plane?
(they scream)
(they shriek)
Looks like it doesn't matter if she's
driving a car or flying a jetpack.
Alex still can't steer!
SAM: I hope she sees that...
...water tower.
(compowder alert)
Clover, Sam, can you read me?
We're in the cornfield.
It's like a maze!
Oh, yeah. I can see you.
Hello!
The corn's been cut in
some kind of pattern.
It looks like a giant sandal!
I'm sending a picture of this
back to WOOHP!
(screams)
We're not coming back from this mission
with aliens,
just with corn dust in our hair!
Just a tip? Don't try that move
during your driver's test.
Right...
- Who's there?
- I don't like this...
Me neither!
(they grunt)
We didn't mean to scare you!
I'm Toby, and this is Jed.
Talk about out of this world!
I'm Sam, and this is Alex and
Clover. We're... corn inspectors.
Were you here the night
there were all those lights?
We sure were! Our buddy Caleb
got picked right up into a spaceship!
We've been looking for him ever since.
- What did the spaceship look like?
- It looked like a kumquat.
- Naw, more like a big ol' rutabaga!
- Aw, you've got hog slop in your eyes!
Do you guys take snack breaks out here?
No, the nearest burger place
is 40 miles away.
Then either there were other humans
here the night Caleb got snatched
or the aliens went through
the drive-thru
- before getting down to business!
- (helicopter whirrs)
- Hasn't my hair suffered enough!?
- Maybe the aliens have come back!
- BOTH: Huh?
- You girls better check that out.
I'm gonna stay here and, you know,
protect the corn.
- Someone should protect them from you!
- (laughs)
Who are you?
And what are you doing here?
We're relatives of the people
who've disappeared.
We're trying to figure out
what's going on.
Ah. Well, I'm Dr. Sagan Hawking.
I'm an astronomer.
Cool! I'm a Virgo!
I'm studying the abductions as well.
If we're facing an alien invasion,
I want to know just
what we're up against.
Anything you've learned
might be helpful.
Oh, we'd love to help.
Well, then hop in. I'll fly you to
my little workshop in the Rockies.
(beeping)
Awesome! Everything in this place
has to do with researching aliens!
"Awesome," or "completely insane?"
You make the call.
SAGAN: This way, girls!
- Hey, what does "GOOPER"...
- I'll take those. Thank you.
Now, if you will direct
your attention to the table.
The stars indicate where
the abductions have taken place.
My theory is that aliens are capturing
members of different cultures
and studying them so they can decide
where to start the full invasion.
There are a lot of countries
they haven't hit yet.
I hope they won't "visit" Beverly Hills.
And my computers are predicting
the next abduction will take place here
in a bazaar in Saudi Arabia.
- Thanks for your time, Doctor.
- Wait!
You promised you'd tell me
what you've learned, remember?
We've learned the alien ship may look
like a kumquat. Or a rutabaga.
I see. Well, I trust you'll contact me
if you find out anything else.
And I'll do the same for you,
of course.
Time to "sheik" our booties
to Saudi Arabia!
Oh, this is my kind of mission.
Undercover in bargain city!
Hello! Focus. you never know
what might be around the next...
ALEX: I think they're not here
for the sales!
Now that's what I call
falling for a girl!
(they gasp)
Nice meeting you guys, but I gotta go.
See ya!
I don't care how good the deals are
here. Next time, I shop online!
Nobody touches my hair!
I could swear I saw that in a movie!
- Just remember driver's ed.
- (horn beeps)
Plan ahead when steering,
identify hazards, signal turns...
...and never, ever tailgate.
- You alright, Alex?
- Totally.
But these guys knew we were gonna
be here! Like, we were set up!
"GOOPER" again!
And look at that burger bag.
Just like the one Clover
found back in Iowa!
Something tells me
Dr. Hawking is connected.
Afternoon, ladies.
Hey, Jerry, does the name "GOOPER"
mean anything to you?
Sorry, it doesn't, but I'll check on it.
However, I do have some information
about the pattern you found in
the cornfield.
- Is it an alien message?
- I'm not sure.
The shapes represent numbers. They're
latitude and longitude coordinates
for an isolated mesa in Mexico.
You'll fly there in this new WOOHP
transportation prototype.
- I'm sure you will love it.
- ALL: Cool!
(they scream)
Iowa, Colorado, Saudi Arabia, Mexico...
I wish we got frequent flyer miles
for all the places we go!
Tell me about it! If there were aliens,
we could go visit them on their planet.
ALL: Huh?
ALEX: Look!
- Aliens! For real!
- BOTH: Maybe...
Cover me! I'm checking this out!
Cover her?
Against the Starship Enormo-prise!?
We can't let her go alone! Come on!
- Got a plan yet?
- I was hoping maybe you did.
Just a second, we're talking.
(they gasp)
Well, here I am. Now what?
Whoa... OK... no presh, Alex,
just the first communication
between our two planets...
Um... hey... what's up?
- Excuse me?
- Did you just speak English?
Actually, I'm better with French,
but I'm pretty good in English
and more than 25 other
intergalactic dialects.
(they scream)
ALEX:
Why have you been abducting people?
We've never done that! It's the GOOPERs!
You know about GOOPER?
There was a distress message
from our friends in the wheat field
saying they'd been captured
by evil GOOPERs.
We came as quickly as we could,
but the GOOPERs were waiting for us!
I must let my friends
know what's going on.
- (static)
- Great. It's jammed!
Clover and Sam. I'm trapped in an alien
ship. Hope you can track me.
Come quick. Love, Alex.
So, tell me more about the GOOPERs.
Are they evil aliens?
SAGAN: Not quite.
Dr. Hawking! Have the GOOPERs
captured you, too?
Captured me? They're working for me!
And you, little spy, are my prisoner!
- But we told you we're just...
- That's right. Concerned relatives?
Please. I saw you land your jetpacks
in that cornfield.
I made up that whole "astronomer" story
to find out how much you knew!
- So... who are you?
- I am the leader of GOOPER!
- Whoa, I had the freakiest dream.
- Me, too. Thank goodness it's over.
(they gasp)
Don't be afraid! We won't hurt you!
Finally!
Someone who doesn't want to hurt us!
Wait... did you just speak English?
Freaky.
- Cool. But, yeah... freaky.
- It's Alex.
ALEX: I'm trapped in an alien ship.
Hope you can track me.
- Come quick. Love, Alex.
- She's trapped on that ship.
The GOOPERs got her!
Just like they got our friend!
Why would they do this?
We would never hurt anyone!
GOOPERs, huh? Sounds like we've all got
a reason to get to that big spaceship!
But how are the four of us gonna follow
Alex with just two Jet-Pack Backpacks?
Leave that to us.
All right, just what is "GOOPER" anyway?
"Global Organization Of Pilfering
Extraterrestrial Resources!"
I tracked this ship over Iowa,
then jammed its equipment.
Now this ship and its crew work for me!
And thanks to the "distress" message
we left in that cornfield,
- I have two ships to aid in my plan!
- What plan?
To create fear! And when Earth is
completely terrified of an invasion,
I'll force the aliens to make "their"
demands: the abductions will only stop
if the world's governments
hand over all their wealth!
What happens to the people
you've already abducted?
Oh, yes, that is a situation.
They'll have to be "disposed of."
In fact, you'll be the first
to test my Obliterator!
Report to me when you're finished.
I'll be in the control room.
(yells)
SAM: Wow! You gave our sky skimmer
a major upgrade.
ALIEN: And it has tracking equipment,
so we can find our friends!
Like, how do you know
how to do all this?
Back on our home planet,
we're an elite team of spies! Let's go!
Dress me up in veils, huh?
Well, look who's laughing now!
- That would be me!
- (gasps / yells)
That won't stop them for long! Come on!
Get 'em!
- ALIEN: How will we get inside?
- We'll just walk in the door!
ALIEN: What door?
- Ha ha!
- That door!
ALEX: That must be the Obliterator!
CALEB: No! Let me go! Help! Help!
Look, that must be Caleb, the guy
who was abducted from the corn field.
ALIEN: They're going to use it
on those people.
Not if we can help it. But how can
the two of us stop all those goons?
GOON: Not to mention us!
There's nowhere to run...
OK, I'm ready to be rescued now.
Are we glad to see you!
Dr. Hawking's behind all this.
I'd tell you more,
but we still have company!
Now it's our turn to help you!
Neat toy! Where did you get it?
From our spy supervisor, J'Ree.
- Jerry?
- No, J'Ree.
- CALEB: Help!
- Up and over, girls!
You guys free the aliens. I'm going
for that big, nasty thingamajig.
Let's see... pulse magnitude,
strength indicator...
Here it is! "Off!"
- ALIENS: Merci beaucoup!
- They speak French too?
And more than 25 other
intergalactic dialects.
Merci beaucoup!
Why don't these things
come with an "off" switch?
You again?
Sorry, I just had my hair cut!
Dr. Hawking's in the control room!
Don't touch another button!
Get them!
(they struggle)
Give it up, Doctor!
Hurry up, girls. She just programmed...
Stay back! Or I'll crash
this ship into Mexico City!
If I can't have this technology,
no one can!
Well, you definitely can't have it.
ALL: Whoa!
- We're going down!
- Tell us something we don't know!
- Steer us clear of the city!
- Me? Steer?
There's no one else, Alex!
Wait a minute!
These controls look kind of familiar.
It's almost exactly like the car
from my driver's ed class, I think!
- Then start driving!
- Maybe if I do this...?
(they scream)
(shrieks) I can't keep her up anymore!
I've got to set her down!
There's just enough room there...
I'm gonna park it like a pro!
(they yell)
(indicators beep)
- Excuse me! Driving is hard enough!
- You got it?
Please return your seats to their
upright positions, we have landed!
I sure hope I'll pass
my driving test after that!
If you ever need your corn inspected,
um, here's my number...
ALEX: Bye, guys! Have a safe flight!
ALIEN: Merci beaucoup!
Maybe someday we can visit them
on their planet.
Maybe. But right now,
you've got a test to take!
(they laugh)
I've never seen a student make such
quick progress! How did you do it, Alex?
I practiced on a giant alien spaceship.
- So, where do you want to drive first?
- Definitely the mall!
I want to see if I can attract three
times as many boys now that I can drive!
(crash)
(cries)
(they laugh)
Ah, man, I guess I still need
to practice with the parking brake!