♪ Here we go, we're getting
on the road till we stop ♪
♪ And then we'll shop ♪
♪ So one, two, three now, baby,
here we go, go, go ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ On a mission undercover
and we're in control ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ We're Totally Spies
so get on with the show ♪
♪ Here we go, here we go ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
If you just tuned in, we're coming
to you live from Niagara Falls...
..where someone is turning
this national landmark
into some kind of dangerous water park!
What kind of sick mind would do this?
CLOVER: C'mon, Sammy,
why don't you blade with us?
Yeah, it doesn't matter that
you're a lame rollerblader,
you can still at least try to have fun.
Ladies, and I quote, "Excess time
spent on recreational activities
could be better spent
exercising the mind."
(they yawn)
I got a quote for ya, "Go fish!"
(they laugh)
BOTH: Huh?
SECURITY GUARD:
Well, well. Look what we have here.
Skaters and violators.
You know the rules, girls.
No roller blading and no littering.
Littering? I was making a wish
and ran out of pennies.
Save it for someone who cares.
Thankfully, a model citizen
alerted me to the situation.
It's them, Mr. Officer! If you want, I
can identify each criminal in a line up.
The only thing criminal here
is your nasty haircut and faux nails.
You can't believe anything she says.
She's a notorious rumor spreader!
Believe me, sir,
I know these girls all too well.
They are repeat offenders
and shouldn't be free to roam the mall!
Now, now. This poor young lady
was merely doing a good deed.
Here.
Good for 20% off anything in the mall.
I'll be back with reinforcements.
Great. I didn't even do anything wrong.
Oh, that's right. You didn't do
anything, Miss... Miss Sam No Fun.
- BOTH: Sam No Fun, Sam No Fun!
- Cut it out! Stop it! Right now!
(they scream)
Afternoon, ladies.
CLOVER: Do you have a blow dryer
in your pocket, Jer?
JERRY: Sorry.
Only WOOHP terry cloth beach towels.
You can take one home as a souvenir
after your mission.
- You'll have to teach me that sometime.
- Sure thing.
Right after you get something to wrap.
We've uncovered something
quite bizarre and troubling.
It seems world leaders have been
creating dangerous thrill rides
- in their respective countries.
- BOTH: Thrill rides?!
In Germany, the Chancellor instructed
the removal of the lines on
the Autobahn. He also added ramps.
Driving has become a reckless,
road raging, bumper car speedway.
In Malaysia, the Prime Minister
has programmed
the elevators of the Petronas Towers
to drop 88 floors.
(people scream)
Lastly, the Brazilian President ordered
cables cut on a suspended bridge.
Tourists were left dangling
above crocodile-infested waters.
Why would world leaders
convert safe national landmarks
into major danger zones?!
Frankly, that's what we need you
to find out.
The Emperor of Japan's wife
is a former WOOHP agent.
Through her, you can get
access to her husband.
Japan? That's like sushi central!
Let's go.
Uh, wait for the gadgets.
One Digit Decoder Card,
one can of
Insta-Freeze Back-off Breath Spray,
a Pocket-Sized Protracting LipSpear,
the Just Sticky Enough Glue Gloves,
the Mini-Lint Vac Battery De-Charger
and CATS.
Cats? I'm more of a dog person...
It stands for
Crystalline Airtight Trisect Shield.
- As long as it's litter box trained.
- Yes. Very amusing.
(they scream)
Hey, you guys think this bullet train
has a sushi bar on it?
(sniffs) Here fishy, fishy...
Let's just hope it takes us to
the Emperor's palace... soon!
I'd like to breathe again.
Can't you at least try to have fun, Sam?
Yeah. Where else can you experience
a nice smooth ride like this?
During an earthquake?
(they scream)
Since when do public trains do
loop de loops?
Can we just get out of here
before I lose my sashimi?
This Digit Decoder Card
should do the trick.
(beeping)
I think we need a little more
purchasing power.
Credit cards...
is there anything they can't do?
(they yell)
- Did we make it?
- I think so.
Hey, there's the Emperor's palace!
ALL: Huh?
CLOVER: Who are the suits?
SAM: I think this isn't
the welcoming committee.
You're making one super-sized mistake,
Mr. Scary Japanese Guard.
I just learned a mean martial arts move
in gym class.
Hold it! I'm Keiko, the Emperor's wife.
These are my guards.
Oopsie.
What do you know? This is
the welcoming committee after all.
KEIKO: Jerry said you'd be coming.
Follow me.
If you need anything, Mr. Katsu
will be happy to assist you.
Sorry, Katsu. I never valet park
the designer originals.
- (they gasp)
- Hello, ladies.
Hello, Mr. Emperor. Sir. Master of
Masters, Ruler of the Unruly...
Goodbye, ladies. Goodbye.
OK. A man of few words.
Too few. I've got a feeling there's
something he's not telling us.
CLOVER: Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's get to the bottom of this.
CLOVER: A palace filled with neat stuff
and we're stuck in this bore-atorium.
Uh-oh. Could be the Emperor.
Get out your Just Sticky Enough Gloves.
You're sure these gloves
are sticky enough?
- What's he doing with that battery?
- It looks like he's charging himself.
SAM: The repeated words, stiff hand
gestures, the battery charger...
- It's like he's some kind of animatron.
- Anima-what?
Ah ha! Just as I suspected.
The gloves weren't sticky enough.
Guards!
(they shriek)
Girls! In here. Quick.
- What was that all about?
- I don't know how to say this,
but we think the Emperor has been
replaced by an animatron.
Oh, my. That would explain
the Emperor's bizarre behavior.
Someone must have abducted
the real Emperor.
You girls must find my husband.
He may be in great danger!
- We'll do everything we can.
- Whoever abducted the real Emperor
must be using a signal
to control the animatronic Emperor.
We just need a way to track the signal.
Wait. I've got it.
- A compact?
- It's a gadget from my spy days.
That thing is anything but light.
KEIKO: A compact with a satellite dish.
A Compactellite.
Regardless, it should track the signal.
(they yelp)
You can borrow the family jet.
It's very fast.
(they yell)
- (growls)
- No, not the shoes!
- ALEX: We must be close.
- (beeping)
- Because the beeping is getting faster?
- No, I can't hold this thing anymore.
At least there aren't any long lines.
SAM: Check out these footprints.
That's weird. The signal seems
to be coming from beneath us.
(wood splinters)
(they groan)
I never did like merry-go-rounds.
OK. So which way is out?
SAM: Not that way.
Oh! Hi. We were just leaving...
Sure you wouldn't rather just talk
this out instead? Didn't think so.
Back off, robot breath!
SAM: One, two... three!
ALL: Cool!
I've had it. There aren't any Emperors
down here. Just dirt and rats and...
- MAN: Get out of my face!
- MAN 2: Oh, be quiet, Mr. President.
- MAN 3: I was here first!
- ..irritable foreign men.
- Locked. There's got to be a way in.
- Hmm. Let me try something.
Now I get it. That martial arts move
was for taking out doors,
- not Japanese guards.
- Whoa.
There's got to be every leader
in the world.
Oh, no. More bad guys.
Relax. We're the good spies.
I've always wanted to say that.
You'd better untie us quickly
before that doctor finishes his plan
and makes us all disappear.
VOICE: Sorry, girls,
but the park is closed.
Hello, intruders.
Welcome to my once secret laboratory.
I am Dr. Eisenstein.
- Dr. Eisenstein?
- Yes, I know.
With a name like Eisenstein,
I knew I'd either have to be a genius
or create a monster.
I decided to do both.
So, Doc. Why replace all the
world's leaders with your robots?
- To show off your hidden talent?
- Hardly.
I've been making animatrons
since you were a little girl
going to amusement parks
just to have fun.
You mean Sam used to have fun?
BOTH: Sam No Fun, Sam No Fun,
Sam No Fun...
My animatrons were the best!
Then came this new invention...
Video games!
Now children would rather
move around a plastic joystick
than see a life-like
swashbuckling pirate!
So, you thought you'd get back in
the biz by kidnapping world leaders
and replacing them with
your machine men?
No, I decided to get revenge by making
my version of the greatest rulers
and programming them to build
hazardous thrill rides.
The world will be
my personal amusement park
until it inevitably destroys itself!
- OK, this guy puts the "reek" in freak.
- Yeah, that plan stinks
even more than your average
evil-doctor-takes-over-the-world plan.
Look at me.
I've been having all the fun so far.
Don't worry, girls,
I promise to make it up to you
by letting you try
my favorite ride in the park.
DR. EISENSTEIN: Now, allow me
to explain how the ride works.
When the car you're in gets up to
15 rotations, the ride will blow up.
In other words, after the explosion,
my cotton candy will have
more of a form than you girls.
Oh, and remember to keep your hands and
feet inside the vehicle at all times.
You wouldn't want to get hurt. (laughs)
Sarcastic much?!
ALEX: We're at the fifth rotation
already.
SAM: Don't worry, I'm sure we'll figure
a way out of this. Soon.
Any second now... The LipSpear!
If I could only reach it...
- ALEX: Thirteenth rotation...
- Got it!
Fourteenth!
Oops. Guess we forgot to keep
our hands and feet
inside the vehicle at all times.
ALEX: Where'd all the world leaders go?
Load 'em up, boys. This trailer's
already late for a date.
Off a bridge, that is. Now,
which robot did I program to drive?
Driving them into the river?
Like, how "mysterious" is that?
SAM: We've got to catch that trailer.
- But how?
- (truck horn)
CLOVER: Shotgun.
They're getting away! Don't we have a
gadget we can use to catch up to them?
Gadget?
We don't need no stinkin' gadget.
CLOVER: Are you sure
this is such a good idea?
No!
(shrieks)
- How does this thing work?
- Like this.
BOTH: We did it!
(world leaders thank them)
What's with world leaders
and their drab gray suits?
Would it kill them to throw
some white into their wardrobes?
Don't worry, we're going to return
you all to your countries.
All we have to do is return the leaders
and deactivate the animatrons
before Eisenstein realizes
he's lost his trailer...
SAM: First stop, Malaysia.
ALEX: But how are we gonna find
the Malaysian animatron?
He turned the Petronas Towers' elevators
into a deadly ride on the tape.
That's where we're headed.
OK, so how exactly does one go about
deactivating an animatron?
This Mini-Lint Vac Battery De-Charger
should suck the life out of him.
But how do we get close enough?
Now I can get as close as I want
to that phony Prime Minister.
Uh-oh. Jerry forgot to charge
the battery. How techno-lame.
Doesn't he know it's like a cell phone?
No juice, no use.
- SAM: That's it!
- What's it?
Your cell phone! We can use the
power from that. Give it to me.
What if I get a really important call?
Here you go. Now be careful,
it might be slightly more powerful.
- Excuse me, Mr. Prime Minister, sir.
- Yes, Soldier?
Uh, are my medals on correctly?
Back off, you creep!
(yells)
Get out of the way! He's gonna blow!
One down. Now let's take care
of the rest of the world.
(cheering)
- Where to next, the land down under?
- I don't know about under,
but we'll be going down if Eisenstein
has anything to say about it.
We've got to protect the world leaders.
I'll put us on autopilot.
- Look out!
- Help me, please!
Everyone stay calm!
We've got the situation under control!
Hello, ladies, so nice to see you again.
Puh-lease. We've taken down
your little henchmen robots before.
Hmm. Yes, that's true. Perhaps this time
they should have some support.
(they yell)
On second thought, everybody panic!
Eliminate them all!
Maybe if we just hide back here,
they'll go away.
That'll teach you to mess with my hair!
We have to get the leaders out of here.
Sucks, don't it?
Spread out!
Huh?
ALEX: Hello?!
You heard your boss. Eliminate me!
I hope you're equipped with
built-in parachutes.
- Quick! Everyone into the tube!
- (panicked yelling)
Time to let the CATS out of the bag.
EISENSTEIN: Help! Help me! Help!
- We really should help him out.
- BOTH: Alright.
Ready to give up your practice, Doc?
(gasps) You're an animatron?!
But if he's an animatron,
then someone had to build him.
Unless he built himself,
but I don't see how. My head hurts.
The real live Dr. Eisenstein created me
in his image before he passed on.
- It was his way of being im...
- Immature?
Immortal. But unfortunately,
he programmed me to self-destruct
if I ever gave out that information.
(slowly)
Well, girls, it was fun while it lasted.
OK, that was, like, totally unexpected.
Look. This must control the animatrons.
Hopefully that's the end of
Dr. Eisenstein's robots forever.
Let's get inside the plane
and get these leaders home.
Hello? Anybody home?
Thank you so much for saving my husband.
Yes, excellent work, girls.
It was our pleasure.
Yeah, it was the least we could do
for a fellow WOOHP spy.
You girls should take a vacation
after that assignment.
Why bother? We've been everyplace
in the world in the last 24 hours.
Everyplace except home.
TV: This week on "Troy's Bayou"...
SAM: What gives, you lamos?
Let's go to the roller blade park.
You want to go to the roller blade park?
Yeah! All that talk about thrill rides
got me psyched up to have fun.
- Go away. I'm wiped.
- Drained.
(sighs) You're right.
We should stay home, blob out,
- and order some yummy take out.
- BOTH: Love it.
Hello? Yes, I'd like to order egg rolls,
shrimp fried rice and some...
- Clover and Alex No Fun!
- Oh, no!
Clover and Alex No Fun,
Clover and Alex No Fun.
SAM: Hey, this is fun!
Clover and Alex No Fun!
Aw, Clover and Alex are tired!
(laughs) Eat my dust!